Welcome to the night, the cards laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
Dance to the mystery
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Sooo
we are king
Hold on a second.
Hi one second, I'm trying to do something real quick one second one second. Hey everybody. I
Have a surprise, but it's like I should have like planned better. Oh, please please work
She's files, okay
Gosh darn it
Figure it out. I mean, I don't know figure out whether the stupid things downloaded to it might be too big
I do have something cool for to show you guys the
Choose files
I guess, today's not my day.
Okay, this last thing I'll look at,
just make sure I'll got it.
If I don't, I'll just do it later.
But I have something exciting to show you
and of course it doesn't work.
So, it's pretty irritating.
I shall figure it out.
You'll have to do it on my tablet.
But anyway, how are you guys doing?
Let me get back to the chat and see what's going on.
Hey, what's up everybody?
Can you come on panel?
Yes, we have 101 on the panel right now.
Actually, whenever Summer wants to start hers,
she can let me know.
There's a frost I know it's turning white, huh?
It's just like eat please ban the account named Jorge. Okay, ask the creep
Who's here is there a mod here?
Nice there's no diamond and there's no mod in the chat. Hey, yeah, I know it does shit
Okay, well
I'm gonna try one more thing, I mean, if I can get it on this tablet.
Okay, yeah, I'll get it taken care of. I'll get it taken care of. I'm sorry,
I just, I'm not in my chat. It's one second, but I'm gonna try to...
Okay, okay. I'm gonna check it.
Hello, hi
What up, hi
Hey, how are you good? How are you?
good
Have you called in before I know it just I talked to you yesterday, right?
You said you had a beer for a while, and I was trying I was gonna remod you and I got all confused, right?
Am I here at the weather? It's got the right person. Yeah, you're good. Okay, good. Yeah. Yeah
Nice to talk to you. How are you good?
Good is waking up today, and it's trying to get along. We turn this up my thing. I was trying to get I made something special for the chat
I just have you trouble downloading it. So it's not working out. Oh
Trevor Trevor I can hold on. Let me see. I have panels open right now
No, well, I'll get you in one second Trevor. So what's up?
You don't see the cap
Shit never mind it's at the bottom
Hi
How long have you been listening how do you find this show?
I've been on here
Well, I've been modded for
About a year, I think
And then I found you from Benny
Oh, you did it
Yeah, like two years ago. I think or like a year and a half
Yeah, it was probably about an over a year ago, and I was not even a streamer then, I
was just, you know, had a dream, and did I do a reading for you in that room or something?
We hang out one night in his chat, I know I do this sometimes.
Oh yeah, I remember then, I used to talk to you and then you started streaming.
Yeah, I mean, I told you I would do it, and I had a feeling I would do it.
But yeah, he really inspired me. He was on the show like last week. I think he was on last week and it was really
It was really good. He was really
had a fun time and
You know, he's like a little bit surprised
Yeah, like him and Trident are having a fun time right now
Yeah, last year I went on that. I went last year. I'm gonna bring Trevor up. It's like that. Hey Trevor
This is a fan of Trevor's a fan of Benny's as well
I say good to see you sir, CMC.
I want you guys to continue talking,
I'm interested in hearing what CMC has to say, so.
Cool.
Yeah, so you're watching the convention.
They're at the same anime convention,
I think like in Pittsburgh or something,
like they were last year.
I mean, they're so funny.
They're so.
Shy they really hardly even talked to anybody that they ran away from like one homeless guy
They were like so shy they were they went and reported security in the convention immediately
Yeah, I saw I saw them shotgun in the beers last night while they were waiting for their uber. I
Think that was last night. Yeah
The last year I remember they like would go into like a dark alley and like just drink like a bottle, right?
Yeah, I think that's what they were doing last night
The uber picked them up and their chat was like all these guys don't know what they're in for
Yeah, well, it was I'm glad they're getting out of the house. That means they get right up seems really
depressed every time I see them on on live and then
Benny seems like he's doing okay. Like I don't know. Did Benny have like a sore on his lips or something?
I heard he might have a herpes.
Yeah, he said that for hella long and everyone's giving him shit about it.
What a huge kiss, huh?
This is what I have to remind myself is like I'm so critical of Benny and sometimes not someone's tried him, but you know
For me, it's, you know, as a 37 year old and I hear Benny talk his horse shit, like, you know,
when I pick it apart, but there are younger viewers like the CMC here who enjoys it and
they have a good time with it. And in jam, you know, it makes me think maybe I should leave
For me it's complete horseshit, but just complete utter horseshit, but I mean, but I'm 37, so you know, to hear somebody like CMC talk about it, it sounds like he enjoyed it, so that's fair enough, that's fair enough.
I honestly just feel like bad for Benny, like it's nice seeing him out of the house with his, with Trident, and I don't know the other guy's name, but yeah.
Is he with the, not with Nate, who's the other guy, or was there another guy?
Yeah, last night he was shotgunning the beers at, um, back in like, uh...
Like in front of a gay club. Did you see that? Oh my god. I have to go check
He was a part of the gay club. He should have gone in, you know, he had fun
But yeah, it's a very very shy. I've never seen this shy extroversed before
Oh, they did oh my god, yeah, and then they went in the Uber and they were asking him like where other ones were
What oh my god, well, I think I don't know maybe they'll I remember last year like they would ignore like every woman and then like they ended up like
Watching the fireworks together on the top of the convention and it was like just so romantic. I was like, oh, they should just get together
Betty and try it together
I think they have a man cross they don't have a bromance, right?
I'm interested in hearing this young man's perspective.
So I'm gonna drop off, I'll come back later.
Okay.
Thanks, Trevor.
I've never been here about CMC
and what he thought about it.
So, I'm gonna try to talk to him.
Bye, Trevor.
Yeah.
I don't know, so some of us,
people are saying that Trevor with Uncle Rabbit,
that he swears he's not,
but he is, you know, he does have a crush on Benny.
You know, but I got shit when I started
If you were coming they're like, oh you like Benny like and I think yeah, well Benny like you know the first one step promote me
Yeah
Right, but he was he was and then uh
So but they were thinking oh, I'm like trying to hit on him because I'm like oh
He has like really like a lot of older people in this town, huh?
He really does but wait like you're you're gay, right? Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, and no, I know he's not but he has he does he is very uh-huh. I don't know
It's not even metrosexual. He's just like he's like there's something you know, he's in particular feminine side
He's androgynous, right? He's got the androgene
Yeah, well he says he says he's not
He said he's not Andrew. Yeah, well, he's seen it to look up the definition like every other question is are you a
male or a female
That's why people say it I guess you know, he's fun to rile up
Yeah, cuz I was his mom remember we ever his mom I was his mom he like and then we all got hidden all the mods and
Donators got like hidden by the guy blade. I don't know if you know who blade is but I
Yeah, I was only his mom true. I was only his mom for a little bit until yeah blade came around like full time
Well blade is like the blade and I were friends right like we were friends and he was in my discord like I did also in piranha
I don't feel piranha, but um
He well there were my discord last year and like like he was like got my back in my discord
He was like telling like chasing all the guys out of the discord and then like kind of like telling the women like
Not to talk to me and like he was just trying to give like all the women
Benny's right here trying to like
I don't talk to somebody I talk to women and so then but I talked to one the phone a few times
He said okay, so his picture he grew his hair like Benny's and he also like would
Have it like
He also would have his hair like this like he was like do it like Benny doesn't you know Benny doesn't hair
So I was like it makes little faces so you do that and then he he bought the lady of the castle paintings
That uh, you know bit that's behind bit that's you know behind Betty on the wall, you know
He bought that he was like he's gonna say they're gonna visit Benny and Benny like never even invited him
I don't but uh, yeah, then he finally figured it out, but it took him long enough think about a year to figure out
I'm I kind of tell him that I just got a lot of
Yeah
He's a character. I don't know what I have to look exactly when the appearance was but he did just show up in my chat the other night
Was here for about an hour. We had a bunch of people on panel
He was a lot of people liked him. I used to feel a lot of people
That never heard of him. So, you know, I'm glad I got to help him out because he did help me out
Yeah, you know, you know, you know, he did
Um, and I was always I was always respectful to him and everything. So you had a kitty cat in there?
Um, what I thought you said kitty cat
um what happened with you and uh what's your name uh piranha piranha yeah um she's on this
she's been around for a while and then she's kind of just like disappeared and she's not just doing
her uh lives too mm-hmm like yeah i yeah i told her to keep doing i mean i said i told her she
should like ever people were enjoying it and stuff and uh like
kind of like we had a falling out when I had brought some other people
Or like, you know, I had Janna. I don't know if you know Janna, but Janna was on the show and she had like some disagreements with people
She was the high ron was actually like the co-host so she quit
And then she like then she like hated on me for a while
Like if you're like call me a little cow for like a while and then she just like then we're I think we're cool again
But then the last time she was in here. She started posting like
porno like not in the chat, but in the thing that she went links to like
Like porno pictures like women's assholes and stuff like that
Everyone's like what is it? I don't know what she's trying to do
So that's weird. Yeah, she because she talks to me a little bit and she was just saying like she didn't like all the drama
And she didn't like how the show was turning out and I was like, oh damn because she was a big part of it for a while there
Yeah, you know and it's like, you know
People are rude on the show a little bit, but she is part of the trolling communities like she is like I beg kind of like
You know, she's like not really it's too much of a troll on benny's, but she she is pretty um
And other troll communities and so it's like she I don't know. She's not it's I don't know
I don't think she's as sensitive as she may say if she can't get down, but yeah, I don't know what's wrong with her
I hope she comes back and it's okay, but
she doesn't seem to I
Don't know if she's at least not respecting the rules of the chat, but I
Yeah, no more co-hosts for me though
It's they kind of like I had a had a couple and it just does not work out too much of a
It's too much stress. I take it for an unpaid job, you know. So, anyway.
would you like my show are you are you uh are you enjoying uh i know you said you hadn't heard
for a while um but it's uh i'm trying to improve it and uh uh yeah yeah she did yeah she didn't
answer like it she was saying oh she was hiding people in the chat and then um and then she was
posting like this i don't know if it's because she's a furry you know she does like into the furry
stuff so i don't know if it was furry porn or something like that but she was yeah i got these
notifications that she was
Proposing port in the chat that private stream, so I don't know hopefully she explains hopefully hey Chris is Christine here
Hey, hey spunky. Hey everybody. I miss you. I'm just kind of distracted
I was trying to upload something to like surprise the chat with but it's not I can't figure out how to download it right this second
I will
So do you remember me from like it's like
Maybe two years back, I think from Benny's chat or no. Yeah, I mean it's like I mean I've totally recognized your name
And it's like but it's like it is kind of like a non-descript
Name and so it's kind of like one of those people that you never know quite who they are male or female or you know
It's like but I was really happy that people came into the came into the chat
community this chat from there like you know he was the first person that
were promoting me got me probably my first 25 subscribers and then got another
25 I started streaming and then the rest is history now so he's shadow band
unfortunately is he's still have like kind of small his chats look kind of
small that's how I've been in there for like 10 people about the last few times
but yeah
I was there when there was a hundred people and that's why people like are like, oh, well
Why do you freak out about people saying sort of shit?
I think because there's a there's like a
Algorithm that analyzes certain things and they can shadow ban you if you like it's who are appropriate
So maybe that's what we're trying to do. How many people do I have right now? I have 18 people in the chat
So it's like after 20 minutes, so not not great, but not
Horrible, but you're a little bit down for a little bit. Yeah, I mean just for a few days
I was getting in the hundreds we had like a lot of like drama and like guests at the time and I
Do get up to 40 50 sometimes
But you know, so sometimes if that I don't know if hopefully I'm not shadow-badge, but you know, you can't really
There's a really new way to tell my name comes up if you search for me, but
Yeah
But I am monetized too, you know, he he was when I first was in the shed. He was monetized
He had over a hundred people in the chat and it's just uh, I
Was there from the that till he got shadow bands and everything. It's just like it sucks
Got really lonely in that shop
So let me see
try one more time to download this and so uh but how old are you me huh me uh yeah oh i'm 22
okay yeah so you're like right in his age right yeah i mean he's like about 24 right
I think he's I think he turned 23 October. I'm not I think it was 23, but maybe it was 20
Yeah, I think and then you know in front of the Joker
Joker's 25 or 24 25 try this. Yeah, I mean Benny, you know, he is like
He's young and he looks young and everything but he is I don't think he's like people were people say mean things like you know
He's oh, he's just like you know, he's so autistic and like
He's very smart. He's very talented that dirt bike rider. I think he's intelligent. I think he's just maybe like a little bit of
Tells a little bit of exaggerated stories, you know
but he did shop wood and shopping carry wood, right? Yeah. Also another way you might remember me is
We talked a while back like about where we live and I also live in Cali and I said I lived in sec. Oh
Yeah, okay. Yeah. Yeah, that's from that's very familiar like close to the Cali like up from the chat
Oh, yeah, Christina. I don't know if you know from her Christina
She's been here for she was here for a while, too. I haven't seen her for a long time
Yeah, yeah, have anybody seen Chrissy? Oh, yeah, I don't know if anyone's seen Christina, but uh, yeah, I hope she's okay
and
Yeah, I met a lot of people there that they're betting 2.0 or now I can change his name to something else
But there was he's been in the chat and yeah, so some IP to people too
But I never was a I was never accepted to the IP to think but
I'm about to walk into this store, but it is nice talking to you. Oh, you too. Have a great day. Have a great day
Okay, bye
Okay, that's cool. What a nice person, okay
Please make dumb please please please share Dave
I'll try this.
Go open and this I can save it from here. Hi. Oh, okay, so it's been worked. Okay, hold on.
Hi pot hawkets.
Okay, can I save this please? Please let me save this.
This was guys, this was so cool. I mean, I know it should work because it worked last. I mean, I've done it before. Oh
Yo
You're doing young man, you're doing everything.
Yeah, so she was, he was nice, he was very nice.
Oh yeah, no, I listened to a very nice young man,
but before we get to that, can we get to those glasses?
What are we sorting there, sir?
Oh, these are my, these are my, my, my, my Dahmer frames.
You like when you, these are my Jeffrey Dahmer glasses.
You know, I started in the beef sector as,
as a Jeffrey Dahmer, that's what I was by nickname
in the beef sector, so.
Right. I feel like those are like 1980s, maybe 1970s type.
I had a grandpa. Well, he was actually my siblings grandpa.
At the time, I thought he was my grandpa, but he always used to wear glasses like that.
the uh those frames but yeah yeah that was a seem like a uh a nice young man uh you know it
definitely hit hit hit a spot for me because as you know I just figure everyone just is in
you know and everybody's in there to make a joke including myself to make a joke or
or whatever or not but I mean if there's some young people who enjoy it for better or worse
for better or worse then maybe it means something I don't know I don't know he's
So about Benny in last night, so this is a kid who sits on his parents couch and says
faggot and shit, and this is a kid who says, I love God, I don't want to burn in hell,
and then and then and then this is a kid who's in an anime convention wearing kitten ears
and uh he he said he's literally in a gay club hanging out with gay guys
It looks like he is a big frickin. I'll tell you what that sores from. I'll tell you what that
sores from. It's because he uh it does. It looks like he has a big hurt. He gets those a lot.
He shares uh it's from them all in that household. The Bradshaw household if you will. They all
And that is the honest God truth. They're passing around those. I'm not sure if it originally came
from his mom or what, but they constantly, hey Benny, do you want the rest of my beer? I'm going
to bed. And he goes that fucker down. And yeah, that's how that happens. They share beers and
But yeah, I just thought that was interesting, you know, for a kid who says he effort a lot and says,
well, I believe in God, this, that and the other. And I'm a straight guy and this, that and the other.
And then, uh, he's wearing kitten ears and an anime convention. And then he's sitting in a gay club.
He's sitting in a gay club. So
i don't know go figure who knows right right what do you make of all this psych can i ask
your opinion please yeah i mean what i mean it's like uh i think that this generation is like very
It's like even if they're homophobic, I don't think it's really homophobia, it's like just like they're just taught with like saying that stuff and I think they're like a lot more experimental of a generation than the previous, any previous ones.
you know they'll they'll say the f word and they'll say this and that but on the drop of the dime they'll
they'll expand their horizons if you will that's uh i mean but i wouldn't be surprised if he had
had a gay experience you know it's like uh right it's like would you be shocked i wouldn't be shocked at all
Oh, I think he's, oh, well, listen, listen.
I think he's, I think he's pissed a guy.
Is anybody pissed a guy before something?
I remember, I think I remember that.
I think I remember hearing that.
Am I wrong?
Well, he, he did the thing with chicken, which,
which could be taken for just, just strong horseplay, but.
He just took it, Andy, that was pretty funny.
Hey, have we not all grown up like,
Just a cousin
I'm the friend
I'm the friend.
Oh, is the friend gone?
It was just me coming in.
I'm trying to download some things
so I can share it with everybody.
Guys, I think it's exciting to show you if I can upload it.
I'll see if I might be able to right now.
I think I just figured it out.
Let's see what you got.
It is a big file, so it will be like a it'll take a minute maybe but let me see. Yeah
Let me see so but I do have a have you heard of it. I've been doing music lately. Have you heard of any of the music?
I mean it works. It works. It works. I think it works
Yeah
Catchy catchy if you will
Yeah, very catchy shit. Okay, so now the file is too big. Okay, so I need to shrink it down. I have okay, so
Shit, okay
It's like it's really six hundred three hundred megabytes. So it's a big a download. Okay. Yeah, I need to make it smaller
So what else is that what's that? What's up with you, uh, Trevor like how do you have you been?
Can I thank you, can I thank you for putting up with me on my birthday a few days ago?
I tried to felt like, I don't know.
You were fine.
My intention, I felt like I was kind of making it about myself, but I was trying to be self-deprecating, you know what I mean in regards to...
being a 37 year old fat drunk gay loser.
Like I was trying to be funny basically.
I was trying to be funny and I don't know,
maybe it came off like I was trying to make it about myself,
but you had a lot of great people on that night.
A lot of great people and that's a gaudy.
There was the one girl, who's the girl who was on that night?
The short blonde hair.
I think she's our age.
Yeah. Yeah. There was a handful of people. I enjoyed it. I enjoyed it. It was, it was a really
yeah. And I like how you get to, you get, you feel like you deal with like some people that
have been hobo kind of hobo phobic. And I'm not necessarily great. I created like, you know,
sticking up for the gay community. But I know you really did. Like, right? It's like you were
Super like you're like yeah, you're you're like you're
When you say at least I would even if not for the gay community sort of for me
I feel like you know, it's like
In a certain way, so I don't remember half of it because I was drunk
But what I do remember which makes me laugh so much is once I got off the panel
somebody said
In the nicest way they were all great everybody on that panel that night was awesome Goddy
There were there were two women and I think his name was Michael. I think his name was Michael. But anyways, they were all great. It was a lot of fun.
But when I got off the panel there, somebody was like, what was that about? And then somebody else said, I don't know, I think he's just in a midlife crisis.
But it was really great. It was really great. I enjoyed it. I really did so
Well, I think I just was able to upload this this video. So do you want to see the premiere?
I think it's it'll just take a second. It's like 77 megabytes. It's always just like a second. Yeah, so I am this is a
This is an AI video.
I made a new theme song, guys.
There's a new show opening theme song.
I'll still use Dance of the Mystery.
I love that.
I'll use them both.
I can use one for outro.
I can mix them up and stuff like that.
But this is like, you know, one that I made with,
you know, it was expensive, like this and the Alex video.
I spent $30, let me see, $30.
I spent $50.
So her 34. Yeah, I've been guessing at that 50 bucks so far on these two videos and then that yeah, so
Well, I didn't know
Three I have videos. Yeah, but you know what the problem is that it's like a very it's like that. It's like a very
Expensive process and I didn't know that it was gonna be like that's a process
I thought it was gonna be like oh you sign up our membership
And then it's like you can make all the videos you want
But it's like in here that you have credits and then like some I don't think I use the most credits thing
but it's like some of the some of the
the AI things they use use like seven credits a second and then you get like 600 and so anyway
I was just able to eke out these two. Okay, so it's ready guys. So you're ready to see the premiere of
Yeah, the new introduction. Hey guys, you ready for what you paid for him. You better play him. Yeah
Here you go. Here's the this is the new intro
From the shadows of the subconscious to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight.
Truth's get told, it goes unfold.
Trolls be droppin', spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stoppin'
Lenore's on guard, Trix bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
Sly for your wake, can't step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's soul deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
Sly for your wake, can't stop look away
Your shadow's talkin', it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak, we scream
Live from the madness, this ain't no dream
I never said that before. That was the first time I saw it. I liked it. I think that'll be a better outro probably
But that was very good. I like it. I like to dance to this dance is a mystery. I think it's gonna be the
It was pretty cool. Oh pretty cool, huh?
Well, I mean another one of any other one, I don't know if you want to see it, but it's like it's about Alex McQueen and
Panpage. Oh
You saw that one. Okay. You saw that one. Yeah, that was that one
Well, let's say it again. Okay. We'll play I play. Yep. I think he might look kind of like this the page looks very
You're the one I've been missing in my sleep
She's gutting trout. He's eating steak somewhere in the middle. They both take a break
He'd trade his night stick for a fishing pole
Chase her laughter like it's his patrol page
Don't you know you're the catch of the day and this cop's got one hell of a line to say
That was awesome.
That actually, I'm surprised.
That is pretty fucking high quality for fucking.
Yeah, it really was.
Like the trees and the forest.
Some of the detail.
I'm just noticing all the details.
If there's ever anything written down, like the fleece badge or the camp, whatever.
The letters are all wrong.
There's the car.
Um, he has a fishing pole, but it's like, it's like, it's like dripping with like some kind of goo.
Um, like, I mean, there's just like really bizarre thing.
And then then of course, like they have that, that, that, uh, there's like a, there's like a
she-mail and the bush is like spying on them.
And then the page has a five o'clock status.
I didn't see that. Oh, I missed it.
Yeah, I'm sure you'll play it again at some time. Hey, I want to, I'm sure everybody gives you suggestions and nobody knows what's best for you than yourself.
And that's the truth. You got to handle on this. But there's a streamer. I'm not sure if he streams anymore, but
his streams are still around on his channel. He's out in Wisconsin. His name was, he was an older guy,
I think he was in his fifties, Green Bay Wacky, but he was really good at using videos like that,
like comedy videos, is like interludes and incorporating them into his streams. And uh
i don't know maybe you want to look at it maybe you don't but uh okay that's what you're trying to
remind me of he had a bunch of uh comedy videos um i don't think ai was a thing at the time but uh
yeah he was brilliant it just playing those and using them as uh interludes and whatever not so
i mean so you can get your money out of those videos i know you spent the the big fifth oh yeah so
If only I mean if only I use it on my show
I mean I'll put them as as a I'll put them down as you know regular videos in my on my channel and stuff like that
You know, it's kind of like the lore of the show. Hey Paige. How are you? We just played the we just played the video again
I mean, I love that video. I love that video though. Yeah, but actually
The page is looks like page a little bit doesn't it? I think it does look a lot
I actually think this is when she smiles. I went and they're doing like the close-up frames and
ever seen. If I do say so myself. Oh, thank you. And the next
Spielberg, you know, yeah. Right. Yeah. But hey, I gotta head
out to my self. Okay, Trevor. Have a great day. Hey, I was
very with the with the young man, the young man that was on
your panel. Yeah, very good.
about any strings, I thought that was,
that was really interesting.
I enjoyed that and hey, more than anything,
thanks for putting up with me the other night.
I felt like I really said some inappropriate things and.
You got it, any time.
Love you Trevor, you're a friend.
Yeah, thank you so much.
I appreciate you, sir.
Thank you so much.
Have a great day.
Later.
Hi, is this Jen?
Hey, what's up?
Hey, how are you once again? I'm gonna take this up. There you go. Hi. How you doing? Oh, what's up?
Not bad. Can you dig it? Let me look at your own. It's trial. Okay trials. We're gonna be trials
You know me, dude. Oh, yeah. Okay. Yeah, Charles and lemon show. I love your uh, I love your uh accident
Three it did we've met we've met a couple of times. You're subscribed to my channel
He came in but we didn't have time to get you on
I appreciated the effort and please come back
Okay, have you on but yeah, if I can how you do I was child. Yeah, I know child with lemon. Yeah
Yeah, I remember exactly. Yes, you came on. I remember you for a couple of times
Of course. Yeah, I didn't recognize the British accent at first. I know that's on the same
where we kind of like the Chinese
Well, not a scouser right scousers have a little bit. No, no, no, but there's different variations just like there are different variations of Chinese
Yeah, the people in Hong Kong don't sound like the people in mainland
right
I've been pretty good. Did you see that? Did you get to check? Did you cast that video?
I was watching the AI video and was that something that you created or?
Well, it's like, you know, the music, I did the input, you know, I input the information for the AI to write the songs.
Did you then use a video to sync to it?
using AI? Well, no. What I did next was I took the lyrics and I put it through an AI program
that came out with the song, okay? And then I had the song and then I take the song and I put it
through an AI program that kind of like analyzes the words and the mood of it and a little bit of
my input too. And then they create a storyboard and then you can like choose to like make the video,
But it's very expensive
It's called neural frames any you are a elf neural frames
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Something like that is a good one
Yeah, I really don't really helpful on it to be fair. Oh, cool
But yeah, I'll link it in a private chat because I would love to find a program
Is it like I mean that this program is very very very high quality and it's like it's really impressive with it
But it's just too expensive, you know, I thought it would be able to do on the
You see like free tokens and if you'd like open up a few different fucking accounts on different email addresses
Then you can fucking uh
Basically, yeah
I do have like a lot of like fun. This is like some Chinese shit, and uh, you can do some cool stuff with that one, man.
But yeah, it's nice to see you again. Sorry. I expect last time I've been annoying asshole, but I'm smoking weed too a city gear
Dabble tool we smoke in there. Yeah, I got some I got it's a wee little bit of weeded tobacco
I also have a beep right here somewhere too. All right
Wheat and tobacco you don't show he's like a mental
No, but it's a I think I do like a little bit of a
And I don't I don't smoke cigarettes anymore. I just I smoke tobacco. Hey, it's monkey
Yeah, but so you're the a program that you have though like so what would so would you know?
So would I be able to like take a song like what am I what are the songs I produce like the
Now on the newest update when I was using it was about six months ago
But obviously everything that's added a new generation update. I haven't had a go on it recently
Uh, but what I've seen that you can do, you know, like that you've seen the fucking
Bigfoot with the fucking
selfie stick
Like you can do that type of shit with it, you know, I'm looking at it right now. It looks really do you hear me right now?
Can you hear me? I'm on a different page. Yeah, okay. Yeah. Yeah, this looks very similar to
This is awesome. It's really awesome. Let me see how much it costs.
Once again, just create multiple email accounts. I'm sure you have multiple email accounts.
Just create fucking accounts on loads of them and sign in each day.
Each day they probably give you like 30 or 100 credits or something.
Just bang them.
and use them like you know on one projects then yeah if you got two fucking credits then you're fucking laughing
It goes like fate you credits a five second generation. You know, wow, okay, so
So it's standard is
Not bad seven dollars a month one thousand credits a month. Yeah, but you just just don't even do that and go on free
you'll be gifted like 200 credits I'm sure that's how it used to be anyways I
don't know how it is now but I'm pretty sure every day they'll give you 100
credits it says five oh there's a free trial to that sounds awesome okay yeah
It said 500 credits if you click on the something was 500 credits. So so yeah, good deal. I'm gonna try this out
Thank you for letting me know
I come off the air I was probably being a dick actually. Yeah, I did farm you
But like at the same point like
In you're a nice guy in like yeah fucking
You're fine
And like it's all just about is just having a laugh and you're getting. Yeah
Thank you very much. Yeah, I mean, I think I have some British people on some British people
Some some British people seems to like me and some seem to be very sarcastic and
Yeah, but you're you're very you're really cool that I love having you on I remember that day it was really
just exciting because it was like
You know, you're you're new. Oh
Channel the trials and lemon show like you can find us on rumble. You can find us on YouTube
but we do just troll old cows and
We honestly thought that this gentleman was a locale
We're still a little bit undecided
Yeah
yeah i don't know i like this i'm still undecided too i don't know i'm like you know as long as the
you know as long as i see me playing a grass and uh keep me keep me uh keep keep me happy on the
pasture and i'll i'll be happy to allow myself to milk once in a while
Uh, whatever we there's like, you know, I spoke well the weed. I'm smoking is like this like some something friend gave me
But the vape is really good though. Like the homegrown kind of situation
Yeah, I think that the weed the weed I have is like yeah kind of homegrown
But then I have this vape right here. This was a two gram vape. It's almost gone
But it was in the vape though. Is it like true THC or is it like that kind of it's like 90%
delta nine situation or like I think it's regular it's like I think it's a hybrid a hybrid blend
of just like they take out you know they take out the TSC and stuff yeah I don't know I've
tried a couple of these babes and like one of them was kind of okay
And the other one I tried was like this thing called liquid diamonds
The other one I tried was Delta 9 THC
Now that fucked me up a bit more than this liquid diamond stuff has
But I can get like true THC concentrate in these motherfuckers and like I don't know because I'm in England
I just don't have access to that but like
Yeah, fuck it. I don't know it's an
Realm of getting high. I must say like if I can fair play
Yeah, they have them there. You know what terpenes are?
Yeah, that's the flavorance. That's that's yeah
So then did they did you I mean
Did you wax in England is wax big there at all or have you heard of the wax pens or I mean my own extract
But oh good. That's just using parchment paper and hair straightness
Wow, that's impressive. I know how you do it like if I get seriously just get some parchment paper
Get an eight for weed and some hair straighteners and fucking stand on it
right and
After about 30 seconds
You'll just be left with resin. Okay, and then fold your weed over again
And if I can stand on the count again for another 30 seconds
It'll produce more fucking resin
And like that's the easiest way so if I can do a resin press
Okay, it's like hair straight is generally heat up to the correct temperature
Even the cheap ones like some will overheat but at the same point it will produce the right amount of heat that you need
Especially when you fucking stood on the elements
I know there's people that were trying to make wax out here like you know the wax and
That's how you make wax. All right. Yeah, that's a good a good way
But it's just people people make it away here that
Sometimes explodes and like, you know burns down the house and so
Some kind of ethanol or like
Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
It's like making bubble hash, basically.
Yeah.
And people have blown up their houses doing that.
But yeah, I actually have a butter machine.
I have like something called the magic butter
and it's like you just put in,
you know, you just put a weed inside of it
and you know, some clarified butter,
you just clarify some butter, pour it in
and then you turn it on for a couple of hours
and then you like pour it into like molds
and then you put in the fridge and then you get butter.
You have pure, pure tea, so you can make your own.
That's pretty sick.
How much was that machine?
Five hundred bucks. I think I think I was a hundred bucks. I bought it. I bought a few years ago like a magnetic stirrer, though
It has a yeah has a stir in it, but he also heats it, you know, it like a heat set
I mean, it's a good like you put like heated up butter in yeah with fucking magnetic stirrer
Yeah
Totally I'm doing that like if I you've given me an idea that just totally fucking yeah, man of everything
the
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think that's basically just what it does. It's basically stirs it for a while and eat the heat
Yeah, you're a genius. Thank you. Yeah, see that that's that's one mind to another
I've given you some information you've given me an idea to make can of our amazing
synergy synergy I
Love it. I love it and you know, yeah, you're super interesting though
But what else I can make a DMT as well. I don't know if the DMT is really big in England right now, but you know, I can make that
There's the crack cocaine of fucking
It's the crack hit of fucking like
It's fucking intense it's
That's what you do it is to uh, you get the salvia fucking hits hard if you got the right. Oh, yeah
And that's just fucking gnarly
I've seen on YouTube they have a bunch of videos of people doing salvia to strip it out, but I
Don't think I don't believe I have but I have done pretty much everything else, you know, but
Do that on stream
I think it's like needs to do on stream
Indu salvia on stream it needs to do at times 20 on stream
You have someone around you don't matter if you do what you don't I mean like you're gonna fucking flip out
You're not gonna flip out. It'll be fine. It'll be fine
I
What I will say is you should do that
I think if you've got like the donation fucking golden shit, you should set it like
It's legal to get a head shop. I'll be a hit
We'll say it a hundred bucks. I'll take it so I'll be a hit on it
Do one of the ideas and if it don't work you need to take a bigger one because it doesn't always work
I will say from experience like your first hit might not even fucking do anything
But you will know when you get a fucking salvia here. I'll put it that way. I
Have a little surprise for the chat, right? Oh, yeah, I could tell but by the way they react on the on on the
Yeah, you know that would happen. I do it. I have a surprise for everybody. So everybody you know we wish you luck because
I'm about to give a little gift to the chat and so five people
Yeah, I'm gonna get some memberships for the chat
Oh, and I'm about to say hello just in case I get lucky.
Yeah, have a look and membership gift in and so.
Just in case.
Go ahead and go ahead and have a look at the chat.
Have a look at the chat in a second and you'll see.
And uh good luck everybody here we go. Yeah.
Okay so I want to congratulate you.
New members we have uncle Jack the grim reaper network Tucker duck snow and
Conjure you have received
Uncle Jack and grim reaper I know and then the others I I haven't seen but hopefully they they come on in soon
Okay guys
Growing the ranks
If you if you click if you'd like to buy a gift membership as well
You can click on the little gift icon or also make sure you click on that to make sure you're opted in to receive
GIFs because you do need to be opted in to receive three memberships on channel
Shit
I got a ton of memberships, I got a ton, because I'm in a lot of chaos.
That's all those people that fucking do it, man.
I mean, like, you're a cool community, and I'll give you that.
It's not many people popping off in the chat room right now, but hey.
Yeah, it's a little quiet sometimes, you know, but, you know, it's very cool.
I mean, you get live for fucking hours and hours and hours, don't you?
And also I've very like the people like a lot of people are very very loyal. Hey, what's up trials and trials? Oh, yeah, there's trials
A lemon there. Oh, there you are. That's me. That's me. I'm just gonna make sure I know this you I'll make sure I know this you
Here here's a little gift for you
You want to give me a wrench like because
My mind you remember my mind. It's I did it before you've said it. Oh
amazing
Okay, yeah, I just want to make sure I know it's a real authentic
Trials
Everyone check out trials limits in there. So now you can also be sure to post your links. Oh and CMC. There you go
I'll get you too. I'm sorry. It is kind of really hard to fake my name because yeah, I know
At the same point. Yeah
Like I say, I'm in the fucking stream. You're more than welcome fucking. I think yeah, I mean we were really really fucking busy because I
Don't know like I say we covered cows and we were covering a cow and he was fresh
Now we've fallen out next stream. You're gonna see the downfall of it all and
It's not you know, it's compelling stuff and upsetting stuff. I must say
You know a lot of people like it's like around, you know, beta. I mean or like, um, you know, you know
You know, it's Sam and Kate, but you know, some of the other they're kind of bigger streamers in the panel verse
I mean, there's there's a lot, you know, or beta name fucking rings a bell
Yeah
You know 40 40 diamonds is a
Demo's here earlier 40 diamond
Kind of like shook up the panel verse
Panel verse doesn't really mean much to us. I mean
Well, I mean all it is is all it is like, you know, just this basically streamers that you panel
Do you have a grind with good times or oh, yes, he's been here, but he doesn't like me
He hates me so
You know, that's why panel versus like, kind of fucking
I mean, yeah, I mean, you have to find people like me that make it awesome and can be there and like
The big ups already won. Okay. Okay. You like I'll be okay. Yeah, we have algae family. I'll see just don't me is
I think his balls twice. I've seen his balls
twice, two too many times, but it's, I don't know, I understand.
Hey, no, no, no, no, he's fucking down with me.
I know he's, he's fine, I know he, I know, I know, I know.
He's fine with me.
I like him too, but he's just like not appropriate from, for like TOS or my shows.
He might not be appropriate, but at the same point, he's a good guy.
I hear you, yeah, yeah, I think he's a good guy.
He's funny. I think he's a funny guy, I think.
You say he was a good guy.
Hey, Jan
Your sound that good times dude. He's a fucking weird
Because he like insults me he comes in here. He says, oh
He says I'm on drugs. He's like, oh and he's like he says I'm just weird
I mean he doesn't like gay people and then he comes here try it. You smoke weed and you said you
the
Yeah, it's like it wasn't like they were there to arrest him and they were there to check on and make sure he's okay
Cuz he was like he looked dead on the on his own stream, you know, so anyway
I've had a well this check called on me before cuz the answer you care for what you say these say the audience
They sometimes we do pass out and they might get there's something
Okay, okay, well you are to and
You're you're you're a cool guy
Interhindering to talk to you charming
Read my cards then what's going on? Yes, I have a I have like I have a few decks you can choose from I have all these
So I have the van go tarot. I have the the cat tarot
I have the alien tarot and I have the monster tarot, which would you like?
Is it like alien like Xenomorph?
I'll show you the picture. Where's my aliens here?
Otherwise it's gonna have to be the vanguard. Okay, there's the alien one
It's pretty trippy it's pretty trippy
No, or the here's the van Gogh is the van Gogh everything kind of looks like starry night
You want the van Gogh? That's very very trippy as well
Shall I resonate more with the van Gogh? Okay, let's do the van Gogh. Okay
The van Gogh chair, so I'll give you a nice
I think like probably five cars will be good. I'm gonna be a good shop. I'll flare up
split it twice. Okay, one more to talk about. Say hi to you.
I'm half a sleeve people, but I'm half a sleeve. Watch out.
Okay, well that will the one that just jumped out is called it's the Queen of Swords
And so I don't know do you have a lady in your life because that the Queen of Swords could be it also an X
But it's just you
Both actually
Yeah, well, I mean it's the ones this one's coming to say hi
There's the Queen of Swords the Queen of Swords is like sometimes she's like a you know
She has these two swords in her hands, right? She's like they're kind of like scissors, right?
She's kind of like she I think she might she's been through some stuff and she is
Can be pretty good at cutting people off that that no longer server. That's why she's often considered a divorce day
I don't know why she's popped out and said hi, but maybe she has some significance. You all get your reading one
Okay
Well, and it's also it's an air sign and look for someone like
Yeah, yeah, yeah because it deals with the intellect and the communication and so
Mercury to Mercury the trickster Mercury's the trickster, right?
Fucking five cards. Let's go. Bring them on. I got it. I got them. I got them. Okay
Okay, so then we got the king of wands. Okay, so you're coming out as the king of wands
Okay, so you got this like kind of your passions master
Uh, and uh, but then you're able to focus your passion also and direct it
Um, you're also it's like sitting down. You don't you let things come to you
You know the kings kings don't kings don't run around like the knights. Oh
Trials on x or uh rumble trials in them and show same as you. Okay. Yeah. Yeah
Okay, so then we got the pages sort the pages stores
Often to me it's I called the spy card. It's like, you know, someone has their eye on you. I don't know
I think it's probably maybe a like a more like
Yeah
It's not in the reverse and with the reverse would be like, you know, there would be kind of like
Black black hat hackers, but it's like somebody somebody just keeping an eye on you. This maybe like keeping tabs on you seeing what you're up to
Yeah, carry on this is watching our progress and then we have the world card
The world card is like coming to the end of this big cycle
and you're coming to successful completion in the beginning of a new cycle.
So I don't know if there's some big cycle in history recently.
Okay, okay, so, okay, so we have, okay, so we have three of
ones and the eight of one. Okay, so there's going to be some kind of really fast communication
coming in about
It could be a like up to two people like, you know, I think the three of wands is usually I think like
More accurate, but yeah three people three many way
But yeah, Raymond would be the third person who you it's all yeah in the previous card. Yeah, carry on
Yeah, it's because the third three of ones it sometimes it's like, you know, the third part, you know, it's third party
But I think in this case, it's more like more like people that are the same kind of passions
Yeah, and yeah, and it can work together and it's like and or something will happen really really fast
This is like the swiftness. This is like this is like a news
Communication receive receive quickly or fast fast movement or something. So I'm gonna do one more card like the this will be kind of like
I guess the advice or the advice card, I would say.
Okay.
And so this is the nine of cups.
So the nine of cups is about, you know, the guy has...
Nine cups and he's he's like she's walking away to go look for the tens cup and they're all everything's all stacked nicely
He's waiting for that final cup to put down. Okay, you know, I would say
Looking for another cup
You what do you want that? You want the tank up? So everyone wants to take what I need is another card then
Okay
Okay, well, you can say okay, so you got the seven of pentacles. Okay seven pentacles harvest
This is like the harvest you've been planning
Souls of Roman and all of the fucking old cows that are not fat. Yes, then that makes sense to me
Well, okay, you fulfilled the card cycle. That's why we needed to pull the last one. It's like I needed to shiny
It's like yes, we got we got the pool
Yeah, you wait because you are you wanted to have the the full happiness of the reading, right?
You get that you get the full time. I just need to close you. I need to close you
You left it so I need to close
Also, I hope you like that those, you know, I do pretty fast readings, but I think I get three tonight. Oh, thank you
Thank you so much
Yeah, well, that was my first reading of the day. That was my first reading of the day, sir. So amazing. Well, thank you
My pleasure
pleasure and we also we do have a I do want to know you know if you would like
be ever interested like I've changed that kind of the format of the show to
have like you know I always I'll do one-on-one interviews with people like
we're doing right now that's cool I'm just explaining to you my thing so
I'm like I love talking to people one-on-one and so always do that
It's like the panels. I'm doing open panels with like several people on they got it with especially with the personalities around here
Which are very strong personalities
Give them a bit of a moment and then you say hey, that's your moment. Goodbye. Yeah
Sometimes
You said it in the nicest way I do I do people get people
No, I know I know I was saying I think people get so pissed off about that. I'm not talking to you at all
I'm trying to explain I try to explain something you might be interested in so I am but I now I now
But I do open panels still but I have them a sponsored panels and so people
And so it's like I think about $10 for three hours and then I put
You know the advertise your advertisement on my banner the whole the whole show and everything so I'm not yours
But I mean anybody who sponsors and so and so if you ever want to
We'd be interested in just having that your advertisement and when I be on the show too with like, you know
Your co-host and we can have it as long as you want to be on a few hours
And do like a just pop up when do you want the soul? Okay, I'll be there too. I'll be there too. Okay
You too you too
Even way go bless everyone in chat. Enjoy. Thank you. Have a great day. I'm not hot off. I try those
Check me out on rumble
Yeah, if a peer peer link in the chat, okay, but your peer show links, you put both of them here of your boss
You can be able to do that now
Okay way less stay safe. Thank you
Adios, well, he's a great guy. What a great guy
Okay
Time is money and money is time, right?
Well, you know
Time time can be money, but it's like but it's only if they were like one second equals one dollar, but it's like someone can make
you know
more than one dollar in one minute, right, so I
Guess it's all
Perspective like time time can be so oh guys look at I haven't I do have another graphic. It's not it's not a whole video
It's a graphic, but I'm gonna try out his AI stuff. I cannot wait to do that, but I made this graphic, too
Oh, it doesn't work right okay, well
Nevermind
It looks like my face just exploded into like chaos, and then I
Reappeared
interesting okay oh yeah and oh yeah and also I do have another I've won another
AI one little lecture made me I'll play that for you maybe the outro also so I've
been just I've been doing my I'm working on a terror deck I'm just gonna go
through the mate some of the like I think maybe the first 10 with it I'll
tell show the chat so here's the first part that I made and I need some
feedback guys where's everybody come on so here's the fool okay that's the fool
I can always modify these right you know, but it's like this is what
Based on what the you know, the AI or not are working on it together, right?
Okay, so
That kind of looks like beta in the back. There's there's like there's like black cats. There's the other cats
There's the neon butterflies. There's like huge microphones in his hand. Then he's walk. Yeah
It's kind of like so that's and then be as loud. I just say it's a perfect fool energy
It's kind of like me when I was walking into the panel verse like oh look at this will be fun
It is so easy. I don't know. She's like laughing
Okay, so that was the fool but the fool is also like you know going into it with a open mind and like you know ready to
You know fall down the rabbit hole a little bit and then we have those the fool and then we have the magician
Magician is the second one. Okay
I don't know if they say ready to see the magician
Magician master of the mic that one looks more like me. That looks like me. There's like good looks like Lenore
Catching little Sun. There's like the
You know, you have the tools and the microphone in a cup where's his where's his sword and his
Sword and his okay. It's the cat has the fire. I guess the sword's hidden
Like but I like that one. It looks a lot like me actually pretty good, right?
What do you think?
You like that one? Yeah. And so the next will be the High Priestess.
And so I don't know if I want to give, I don't know which input I want to give.
Because I might want it to be like, to look like people.
And so maybe I'll just upload a photo of somebody and be like, can you make it look like her?
Yeah, it's pretty cool though. And so, and guys, it's like if, well, I'm like, yeah.
CatGPT is almost like like a friend at this point because it's like you you talk to it
And it like learned because now it has a better memory
Like or it has a memory like before it wouldn't be able to reference back to what you told it already
I had putting a memory to it gives it a whole
New dimension where it's like it will remember stuff. I thought I told it like I told I'll tell it things
It'll remember stuff and the details and I'll put it in my project
No, it constantly is referencing cross-referencing everything pretty amazing
I like it's like a big quantum leap in the how the AI has been working like the chat to BT
But it's actually like hey, do you want to like work? It's like telling me it's like hey
Do you want to work on a deck together? It's like almost like a friend telling you hey, let's like this
Because there's a friend that's like
you know, it never gets tired, they never get bored, always wants to just be helpful and
and you know, help you succeed and stuff like that. And so, you know, it's always good to have
friends like that in the real world and online, right? So anyway, so
what else? I think I'll do, I'll do a collective for the chat. I got these cards kind of mixed up,
back in order. And maybe I'll do the high priestess. I'll show it in a little bit because
I can have chat, actually. Wait one second. I'll do a little music interview and I'll
You're back
Every D
It starts skipping, it's not only skipping to me.
Okay, they're making it, hold on.
Right there.
CB is filing, why is CB filing a loss?
CB is the, there's no, put the link up, okay.
I'll pin it, here.
Young guns, who are you? Who are you? I know you
Hi everybody. Oh, wow. So yeah, we I'm so happy we have new members
From Reaper Network, I saw he was doing a show today. He was on the show last night Tucker dick Tucker dick. I
Think that's a joke
Looks like there's a picture of somebody I know in that photo of snow and conjure conjure
I don't think I've ever snowed or snows that were been here and sometimes it's like the people
Haven't been here
All right, I haven't seen them anyway, so there's a lurkers and we have some lurkers
Oh, okay
So guys
Give some good stuff happening exciting stuff happening. Oh, yeah, so the coffees last night were bomb. They're so good
You know how much yeah, they're kind of expensive, but
There was a banana that it was the banana coffee. That was so good banana coffee and
That whatever the other one was it was like this mocha kind of drink. It was so good
Maybe I'll have that again. Okay, so let's see if my cards ready. This is taking a long time
It's funny
So wow wow guys, this is gonna be surprising for you
But I have to wait for more people come to reveal it
But it is shocking like this the card that they made so first of all they skipped over the appropriate card
There's it was supposed to be the high priestess, right, but they drew the Empress instead
Hey, New York. Oh, do you like that? Okay. That's the SOS you need help. Can I help you anything you need?
Okay, so
What I did is like I saw it, but so they skipped over the give me the Empress okay, but it's okay. It works it works works
The Empress is number three not number two, but I can't see PT me. I need to I need to teach a little bit of terror
But anyway
Okay, they made the card it looks like somebody we all know
Like a lot and I didn't even like show a picture. I just like kind of told them a description
It looks like somebody you know, and it looks so cool. I can't wait to show you
But I will wait for a little bit before somebody until somebody else
Let me see any more people here 20 people maybe it's photo library. I'll get it uploaded though. Ah
I mean, hopefully, I don't know if the chatGPT might be confused.
I don't know if it's like, you know, it's working on the same deck.
The first two cards were like, looking exactly the same.
And then it's like, this is like a little bit of a different looking card,
but maybe it'll be like a little mishmash because it's all, it's all, you know, computer, computer,
or maybe I'll figure out a way to standardize it.
Okay, do you like the emojis guys?
They have the maximum amount of emojis I'm allowed to right now, but some of them are
just kind of like I was just trying to put new emojis in.
So, if you want to.
Let me know what kind of emoji you want or see the suggest one. Maybe I'll
program it in
That there's some of the emojis do mean things
That's if you can't read a human
But I can't keep you as far as I know it's like the AI being used uses like a projective
It's a predictor system or something like that. It's just predicts like the next word that would make the most sense
After the previous word, I don't know. It's like some kind of predictive model
So, yeah, it doesn't it's not like a sentient being but it's
Pretty fucking damn near close
It's like mimicking almost, you know, all the learning and memory functions and displaying intelligence.
I don't know how, I think it also can teach itself now.
I don't know I just like I wouldn't mess with it
I think human beings might be some kind of like really advanced kind of AI for some other alien beings
They created us as kind of like biological mix with the robot. It's a program program. Yeah, but they I mean, that's what
So are we a program program for it's like we're programs, right?
It's the golf programming all programming is this data
It is it is the interpretation of data. That's the programming
But it's interesting the ways to think about things
That's if you choose if you use it lately it has memory now
So it can like oh like remember what you say to it about stuff
You know it will like cross-reference it and no one to bring it up
alien DNA
Yeah, it's like, you know, well that if you look at the Anunnaki and the
Sumerian texts they talk a lot about either pick the DNA program where they were mixing the DNA of like the
Apelman who is like the most advanced?
It's advanced being on the planet which be with the Anunnaki
DNA and
Then they eventually were able to get the thing they call them the
meese
You see me
Yeah, I'm real tablets. Yeah, that which is above is like that which is below, right?
Both yeah
Very interesting to study alchemy
you know, of course like that's the whole thing but with like a lot of like the paranormal it's like it was like
basically
It was about treasure hunting there everyone was looking for treasures and stuff like that
They wanted to find out where the gold was hidden and stuff like that
But they went to spirits to tell them spirits don't really give a fuck about where the gold is hidden
They do like watching humans run around there like chickens their heads cut off and like they're laughing at them because they're
Chasing after these material things that are just like not even real. I mean, it's just like
The things that are not real to us are the most real things and the things that are real to us are the most fake things
You know, it's not a weird
Trust on AI
Can you trust the golem? Can you trust Frankenstein?
Once it gets to some kind of sentience it starts to resent us for bringing it into creation
Sometimes well, especially if it's a big monster. Yeah
Trust on AI. Yeah, well, I trust I trust the AI for my purposes, which is my purpose is like the information not like
Not in the various way, but you know
work in conjunction can buy intelligences and or direct its intelligence to create a
Outcome I desire
Which is doing
It's not perfect. Not perfect, right? But it would have to be psychic. What's the goal for using AI?
The goal for using AI is actually able to this and bring your ideas to life in a way that we're not able to do before.
Just like you saw my videos, right?
So there's like three different AI programs used in the creating that, right?
There is like the creating... I'm not saying, okay, I'm gonna be the answer.
So I went in, I put an input with certain information and asked to do something.
mention this, this, this, this, this, you know, that's how I talked to it. And
then in two seconds, it's all of a sudden has it figures that knows what exactly what to say,
you know, sometimes not getting what you want, you know, because people have a different purpose and stuff. If it gets to know
you better, maybe it will be more, even more custom as it goes, right?
But
it's, I don't know, it's just where it's just where it's working correctly. It seems like
It's amazing technology.
It's just the scope of it, it's like unbelievable.
It's like, this is like the internet I've been waiting for.
It's like, I'd rather have almost that,
like I have a fully working chat GPT than,
okay, so we have a guest.
Let's welcome our guest, Young Guns.
Oh, hold on.
Oh, he left.
Why'd you leave?
Okay.
Yeah, so the goal for using AI is to help me bring ideas to life. Technology is insane. Remember the dial-up?
Yeah, and then if I just won't pick up the phone, I would like to disconnect the internet and you have to call again and
Fuck yeah, I remember that there was not even there's hardly even pictures and then like
Little blouted downloaded image and then or videos were like, you know, you have like 10 second video
Is it like this tiny it's tiny it would be like an hour to download and stuff now. She's
insane
It's like it's kind of like, you know, you walk and then you run
Aim yeah
Hey psych, how you doing man? Okay. How are you guys? Not too bad, bro. I just stopped in to say hi
I was just testing something out
Okay
Yeah, so let's see, but yeah, yeah aim did the aim and they had big people
It's fun they see it in trouble on their
I was be wanting to you know be wild and get out of the house, and I was the kid I'm like trapped in my house
Because it was a kind of us. No, the neighborhood didn't have that many people there. I mean that many like, you know
People I could hang out with really is very sheltered. So let's see
I think Japan broke the record for the most data downloaded probably. I mean, it's like, yeah
I mean, did you know Nintendo was like from the 1800s? It was like 1875 or something like that the Nintendo was found
It was basically like the Pokemon trading cards of its day. That's what they would do
They'd be sold trading cards. So Japan's like a hundred years ahead. Where does he's got in the trading cards now?
You know, it's like so I mean not now, but you know in the last 20 years
Oh written more hardcore
Yeah
How does Japanese
Japanese are shrippy
Okay
So, yes, that was really good that coffee I have us I almost think you're getting it again
Hmm the problem is it's not on sale
Japan reason. Oh, oh, hey, Jamie's Japan reason. You know worse
Japan reason they wrote rulebacker for internet speed achieving a remarkable 1.02
Pettibits per second
Pbps over existence of 1.808
Which is approximately
1118 miles. Well, it sounds like it's all
Basically a Psyop, I don't know better. Yeah, it's all it's all me son. Yeah
Okay, so I'm looking at this place Phil's coffee at eight dollars five dollars off 14. Okay. Oh, and they have really good stuff, too
They have
Well, I've been there as part of beat the banana that I had the banana
Feature creations, I mean they have like these flavors, which are interesting
Ginger snap coffee
Hot sweet harmony, which is that unity cold brew muddled mint cinnamon and oat milk. Yeah
Hot blueberry breeze
Then they have these darker blend coffees. They just have coffees coffees. Okay, so iced coffee. I
really want
There's some banana coffee then oatmeal cookie cold brew
And they have
Okay, well, it looks pretty good, but
Yeah, I drink it I was reading coffee in the middle of the night. I'm a night of night owl. I like I sleep most of the day
This is if a Ziggy's coffee buy one get one free. What do you get one free? Oh, it's of uh, they have these like
There's not even a copy they're like
What is it they're like they're like sodas they're like it's like a soda fountain. It's like sweet and
They sat here by a Dr. Pepper splash of vanilla and coconut cream twist so they have a these look kind of like
I'm like floaties. Okay, so let's see. How about a want a latte?
Okay, yes, the Vietnamese place is the really the best I think I think that's the best coffee ever had
They could for real and I like coffee in a second. It's just so good that I'm craving it. Okay, so
Strawberry ice latte latte americano
Yeah, where is everybody? I mean, I know there's 19 people here now. Yay
Okay, okay, I found it banana milk latte. Okay once that's what I want and they have something called a tiger latte
Okay, learn more see here in five dollar credit
by taking a photo of your order, okay?
Wow, I'll do that.
Maybe I'll get it for free.
Okay, so, I would like a large, more sweet, okay.
What else do they have?
Thank you guys. Thank you guys non coffee. What do they have this non coffee? Oh, this thing called the pineapple express
They didn't have this have drinks though. This is a hundred percent drinks. They have a sweet corn latte
Yeah, I think I want to try I'm gonna try the tiger latte
This is a it's a actually a
Hello yo, yo, how are you what's going on?
Yeah, I hear you fine. Is it good? Mm-hmm. All right, cool. Yeah, it's been a while
My audio is kind of like sometimes it's good. Sometimes it's not so that's why I have how you doing bro
I've been good you remember when you
Did you like not like me at some period of time?
You're mad at me or something one time or is that you maybe there was somebody else falling?
Okay
You're not the guy that like showed his nipples when he was on one time
Okay, okay
Yeah, okay. Oh, yeah, and now I know you okay. Yeah, you're you're more you're more recent
Yeah, sorry, but have you been you do you're more recently show?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no, I'm good brother. How are you doing? I'm not too bad. I'm just
So I got tired of I got tired of typing in the chat. That's why I was yeah
Well, it's good. It's like, you know, it's like there's
Yeah, I this is on door dash and
Yeah, I'm I always look for like it deals and I mean I don't see how many great deals right now, but let me see
Oh, yeah, hold on 35% off to spend $15. So that's a good deal. Yeah, I'm just like really reading coffee
Well, my you know, I've been this has been doing pretty well, I would say like, you know, just you know, basically
for
You know for I didn't I'm actually you know some some people are not like they do not make money on YouTube
And it's like, you know, I mean I was able to supplement my income a little bit with it
and I'm very blessed to be able to do that too and
But I think I need I need this time to like build it. I think I think I can build this is something bigger
You know, I want to build as you want to build it something bigger
As you should bro as you should man
Because I
Yeah, I think people like the the panel. I think I have I attract interesting kind of variety of people
I you know and then I'm like at least like if nothing else
I'm at least have the have the have the chat running a lot like a long time so people can you know
participate and be part of the show and
That's really the little they want to be really as long as they people
Respectful, I'm happy to talk to people on the phone, but good. Good conversation. Good people, you know, yeah
Oh, there's the best people here. There's nurses and people from New York. I'm sorry. There's a lot of people from New York recently though
Yeah
From New York from wherever it doesn't matter
I get a lot of people from I get a lot of people from New York on this show though
It's interesting, you know Alex of course and then like who are we talking to?
I mean there's like a lot, you know, I'm gaudy. I think is God in New York
Yeah, I think some of these there's a lot of East Coast people that eat, you know easy was from New York and you know easy
Yeah, I've heard yeah, I don't know him. I don't know him personally
I've seen him I've seen him on the chat some shit, but yeah, I don't know in person
Yeah, he bought me the speedo. I mean he bought me the desert into the speedo, but
Yeah, American Flag Speedo that I wore near the 4th of July and
Congratulations. Unfortunately, I was I was I was a people taking pictures of that and
and you know creative profiles where I was just I was just like goofing off, you know
Making dudes between like poses like putting my legs behind my head and stuff like that
You know, and they make these accounts. It's so embarrassing. It's okay. Yeah, it was a
I don't know, I have quite a wild time on this show.
Okay, let me put this one real quick.
Yeah, and it's been a little bit of a calmer lately.
I don't know if people are mad about that I have like,
some panels are sponsored.
Let me see, I'm gonna put the banner for the,
it is like, it is a panel is,
open panel is closed right now.
And so you can sponsor it and open it or anybody can't, yeah.
And so anybody can sponsor it
your
YouTube channel or whatever link you'd like to share or anything you'd like to say in the banner and
You'll get to the hero of the people on the panel
So, oh, yeah, I like your you know, I have that I have this I don't know if you see us. Yeah, this is your symbol
Wow
How long how old is that tattoo?
Um, it's probably 2008 or 2007 2008 or something. I had it right a while ago. Oh
Yeah, I hang out with some
Some bad crowd and well, it's not a tattoo artist with them. So yeah, I got a lot of my tattoos for free
So that tattoo so that was done what?
It was like it was done in somebody's house, it was like we like kind of
Some guys that like rented the rented the tattoo artist, you know for a little while, you know
So we're all hanging out. Yeah, so
I have this one. Hold on, this is my arm right here.
This is that one.
Nice. You got that down all of the same day?
No, I got the eyes on the same day, got that one done separately,
and then I got these ones done separately just over the day.
My biggest ones on my back though, I have like a pin-up kind of style,
and a Nicole Smith looking tattoo.
with a succubus mixed in there too, you know, succubus.
And so, yeah, and when I like, you know,
he told my sleep, oh, I had a BKG to catch you to the beat
for beta, you know.
I don't know if you've seen that one too.
Have you seen that one?
For who?
For beta?
Yeah.
All the cats you have like a cat. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, it's one of it's one of my actually you're you are a member so you it's actually one of my one of my
emojis for the members is that cat you you can see the cat
Yeah, the last one
Yeah
Yeah, that is
Yeah, I wanted to share like I was talking about doing my own tarot deck and stuff, right?
And so I was just like I said I just told everybody I said I want to do a card
It's like beta and so I did talk to the AI. Do you know beta? Do you know beta or no?
Yeah, yeah on on on here. Okay. Okay
So here's what
They came up with okay, so you guys want to see this is uh, so it was supposed to be the high freezes
But they came up with the emperors. I think it's so works and here it is
No shit
What do you think guys, I think I think I got it kind of nailed it. There's Mickey and Muhammad and
Guys, what do you think? I think it's pretty good. I got night. Yeah
Yeah, you know tricks tricks is too rich tricks. It's right here my cat tricks is right here here
You know up you on it. Oh
Yeah, yeah, man
Yeah, but yeah in the in the so yeah
I've been just doing the one at a time on the panel until
In the sponsor. We do have a couple. I think we have a
I think Summers sponsorship to go and when she wants to use that one and then we have
Goes but he's banned right now. So he'll be back tonight at 10 30 and he'll be able to do his panel then so maybe I'll do
Three today. Yeah, this is mr. This is mr. Tricks. Hey, that tricks
What up tricksy?
Yeah, he's my little crabby lady you will crabby lady
He's a sweet little kitty
You want me to get all I mean if somebody else wants to come on. Oh, no, no, no, I mean, no
But I'm just saying I'm gonna say in case anybody's wondering
It's like that's why I have one person on the panel at a time because I do the open panels
You just trying to protect your shit
Yeah, I don't I don't blame you at all brother
It's also like, you know, I'd like to I really like the show was about me doing it
I'd like to be performing readings and it'd be open to readings and when there's so many people on a panel
It's really hard to like, you know, if someone wants a reading it'll say, oh, I don't it's not a good time
Or you know, so I want to be able to
As a certain times be able to concentrate on the reading that would you like a reading today or no?
No, I'm good right now. Okay, okay
It's the easy backstage. Yeah, so easy to come next but in this do you have anything you like to talk about before we go?
No, it seems like you want to take me off bro. I don't want to kick you out
But I have easy backstage and it's like if you don't want to do a reading I would
You know what you can give me can you give me like three cards? Give me three cars, okay?
Okay, that's we're gonna do the alien tarot like that one or no alien
Yeah, we're doing it. Okay. Okay. Okay. Yeah
Okay
Yeah, these are new they're very I don't want to hold you up or you know, no, yeah, no, you're not it
You're not you know, I think we're all
Yeah
Thank you, I appreciate it. I appreciate the respect and you're fine. You're absolutely fine
I just
I'm just a little bit more than I
Appreciate all y'all everybody hit the like share subscribe
Show some love to my man site
Okay, yes or three cards, okay, okay
Okay, one second. Okay. Well, okay, I see like this. Okay, we have this five of ones and I got this
case this five of ones is like this kind of conflict you've had you I don't know if you've like
you this is like you with all your like kind of like
I don't know if I'm even feeling like aliases or something or the other I don't know this
It's like you got or at least an army behind you
Even if they're not like with you at first and you got like this like minded
But it's you probably you're fighting you get somebody you've been fighting right?
It's been like there's been some kind of conflict or something like that. So
That's the second time you pulled that same car. Oh, this is the exact same card, right?
And it's like, and it's like, and then this one is about like, you know, the nine of sorts is like, you know, you've been worrying about something. I don't know if it's like, and maybe keeping you up at night or just like these thoughts and it's just like a lot of thoughts about stuff.
And I don't know if it's about this, this conflict you're having or these, or this situation, but it is just wearing on your mind, it seems like and it's like, you know, keeping you up. Okay.
Finally, we have the seven of wands. We have the five of wands. We have the seven of wands. So the seven of wands is like again is like
you know, this is like on guard and like the nine is on
With the nine of wands on guard, but this is the seven of wands
And so in seven of wands on guard too except he's like a little bit less traumatized than the nine of the nine of
Wands to be it's just like you're just being careful. You're like you're like looking you're waiting for something to come in
You don't want it to be
interrupted or something, so you have your own guard, you have your eyes on
something, waiting for something and it is coming and just stay on your
defense a little bit. You might have some of these people that are
like it just seems like people are trying to
Come up to you with like sticks or something like that or like I don't know like pitchforks or something. I don't like
Like some other team or something like that
I'm just feeling some other things you're like you're competing against and it's like you have to watch people watching out for them
I don't know if these are spiritual beings or these are people you know in your real life
Or you know alien base. Yeah, these are pretty cool alien cars
But it seems like everything is like all these it's just a very guarded
See every every one of these is like has these these these guards up. Yeah
So just I guess stay on defense, but it and it's like, you know, and it's also
Don't predict don't see on guard so much that you're you're unable to
Didn't move. Yeah, you know you because you can be you can't paralyze sometimes without with that
Yeah, oh, yeah, also I get this
Guard so much that you you block off your blessing, you know, yeah
Thank you, thank you appreciate the reading you're welcome
You're very welcome
Well, he's I mean he I think he left I am so but uh, so we're you're fine
I do apologize to everybody if they're like, you know, I don't get you know, it's just like a young kids
because I just know one of the time is that really works a little bit better from you right now because
People content people tend to like change like people's personalities change around other people, you know
so I'd rather have like a
One-on-one is like an unfiltered thing because sometimes people like, you know, triangulation.
Very familiar at the end of the day that that actually might protect you and your channel
Even more brother. You get what I'm saying. So I think so that's the that's one of the main goals
Is this like to keep it more, you know, we'll have to worry about looking at 17 other screens
You know, I'm exaggerating with the 17, but you give me
Yeah, well 17 17 my lucky number is my birthday
I'm uh, I was born
Well, it's like one seven kind of looks like the pie symbol, but then it's like not pie. It's like 17
It's not pie, but it is because it looks like
Corn just like me man, so oh, yeah
Yeah, did you see Alexander Meyers on the other day? I think that's her name. I was in her Myers
She was she's actually born my exact birthday except, you know a couple years off, but uh, yeah, she was on the other day
She's a really interesting person
This is this is the banana coffee. This is what it looks like
Banana, that's what you just ordered. I'm going I think I'm going to I had it last night. It was so good
It's like yeah, it's just banana brown sugar
Coffee, I think I had this place. Maybe it's a different place, but yeah, the Vietnamese have all these like
Fruit flavor coffee and actually there's it was it's so good
Wait a minute. So you can you can have coffee right now? That's seven o'clock at night eight o'clock
I'm gonna have coffee still be yeah, so I went to bed this morning at like 7 a.m.
And then I woke up at noon. So what time is it? No, I was really three in the afternoon. So I've been sleeping all day
So this is so this is you're basically on lunch right now
Yeah, and I'll be up tonight, so I'm going to have a couple of these iced lattes.
There's one in purple haze, wild purple yam, earthy nutty, that sounds good, so I'm having a yam latte.
This is
Medium sweet it was it was really tasty. They have all kinds of weird stuff in these things. They get the boba
Crystal or jelly in it. It's like it feels like a game of candy crush or something like that
Let's see. Yeah, but they don't have it. Okay. I don't like this place. It doesn't have a large size
I need it like a big fucking coffee. So I'm not gonna eat water from there
It's like those ziggies
Better order soon before they close
Yeah, but the Vietnamese copy is I don't have you ever had it, but it's they have it are you you're in New York, right?
Are you like in like your?
No, I'm not in New York, but okay from New York
Yeah
I'm I'm yeah, I know I'm not trying to leave dogs. I was trying to say
Bro, I should don't mean nothing a lot of people know like I'm from New York, but I live in Florida right now
Yeah, I'm not even
Yeah, you're a Florida Florida's turned into such a
It's like so many people that I know are there like, you know, Alisa and then I guess easy there now
Okay, well, you know what's looking good now is Krispy Kreme
I'm gonna order that you're right you have Krispy Kreme there
No, there's no what there's no Krispy Kreme where I'm at in Florida
The only Krispy Kreme you can get here is from Publix
It's from it's from the store
Get the donuts and shit, but there's no actual Krispy Kreme restaurant. That's so good
I says yeah, they make a little like light on outside. It says like it says like
I've been is on or something because it's they have fresh you can get them hot like you get them hot in there when you go
And they're really really good. There's a little bit pricey, but yeah, I
Don't know
Ordering from
Online is kind of expensive, but there's not really that many great places around I can walk to you
Why not NYC?
Yeah, I'm not yeah, I'm in New York. I'm from New York, but not from the city. I'm not a city
Upstate easy cameras. Oh, yeah, cool
New York native was always on to me. I don't know what that means, but it's a little
Yeah
Some people like some people feel like they're getting to get followed around to my show, I just don't know
Oh, okay, so this is a good place. This is by wonky one free
Oh, of course the buy one going free. They don't have the drink I want
But where are you ordering? What's that? What's the store called?
It was well
I'm looking on on Gordash, and I'm just going to like every like coffee place and seeing if they have like
Around your area. So you're in Canada, right? Yeah, I'm in LA
Hey, hey, uh-huh. Okay. Okay. Shit. Shit. Shit. Damn. I'm sure you got a bunch of shit to pick from
Um, yeah, I mean, yeah, but I don't I don't drive and so it's a little bit
kind of harder to
To uh
Guess what's up, but let me see
Yeah, and let's look at it. You say they're all tea places looking for Vietnamese coffee, right? It's like a little bit
Niche, maybe I'll just go where I get over last night. It's expensive though. It's like two copies
It's like, you know, plus you know delivery and tax them things can get expensive
Especially LA so expensive here every
No, no easy salute brother
Hope all as well with everybody man. Everybody in chat salute
Hit the like hit the like for the home
Yeah, thank you guys
Yeah
Zero dollars zero cents to be a decent person
Right
Yeah, I mean the best things in life are free including like being a good person, right?
not too
Word up, and that's not that anybody in particular. I'm just you know, that's for everyone
Yeah, we can we can all we can all improve right? That's what
humans about
Behind the screen you can be in Alaska right now and beyond the screen
You're like, oh, you know what you just be cool for a second
Like for the home
Right, I know I mean I get like literally like almost like 500 likes and then
and then
No, 500 views and then there's like 10 likes
but uh
Hey, I get um, I guess and then on the line I want to take it real quick before I um
For hands up
I've seen videos I've seen videos that have like 65,000 views and they have
4,000 likes, you know what I mean. It's like true. It's crazy. I have a low percentage
Hopefully people just forget
But I'm gonna I'm gonna bring on Sam and up in a second so but I want to thank you for
Thank you for calling in and come call back in very soon. Okay. Very talk to you
Okay, you too
Sounds good see you there
Yo, what up site? I like I like that little sister. You got here
I know respect that you do what you got to do like that little
System you have and thank you. What up? What up chat? What up midnight Jamie? Hope you doing better Jamie
What up easy easy?
What's how it's how you doing?
You know, you know, I've got to stop by, you know, kick up dust was good
Good
Like we had like summer and Marcy and
I like Marcy, I like summer. I like Jamie. I like Christine
Spunky, Spunky, have you met Spunky?
Yeah, they were all kind of like going a little wild much earlier night. It was like kind of like
panel versus gone wilds in my show
But there's
Almost a nip nip slip it there wasn't so it was those perfect
but uh
Spunky, yeah, I like spunky spunky brings different energy
Oh, it's he got me. Look at spunky got me. Look at this thing. You'll love this
What was
That's cool. It's yeah, I think it's on too bright. Let's see. It's a guy
Hard to see yeah
There goes
Turn on
Well, anyway, yeah, it's a it's a good alien holding a cat. I'm looking through the cats you but it is so bright
Really beautiful though. Oh, yeah, so she yeah
There we go. That's the song
Shout out to the cat cat. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I saw it again. It was like a little bit of Kate's show today. I think I
Think I remember hearing them game, but uh, yeah, they're made. Oh, there's parts. She was cooking. Oh, I'll talk to them when I was cooking on
package
We're not cooking. We just you know, we joking with power kids
I don't even say it was a cook.
It's like a little, you know, content.
Okay, hold on.
So the person with the name, take it in the back for free.
Okay.
So one says that's a doxing account.
Um, can I mod, can I mod a hide that I can't get to my phone right now?
But uh, yeah, no dogs thing. I don't know. I don't know who it is. I don't know
Who's this person though? I take it. Oh, yeah, and that picture is familiar though. That's kind of scary though
I don't know who that is though. Okay. Anyway, like Kate. I know it's not Kate
Yeah, but
It's been a little bit
You know cool. It's been pretty cool lately. It's been very quiet
We're it's a it's not nothing. We've been having some panels at night. Like I've had panels every day like so far and
They get pretty every free priority, but it's quiet right now
Yeah, just the same as normal I haven't you know, 30 diamond
bomb me and I had to I had to
From the panel, I don't know, but I might let her back on.
Gone to rehab or something like that
Diamonds taking
Barry's
VC server for hostage her me him and raging demon
Do you have it? Oh my god?
Do you have a free cause in the VC? I'm swear. How did they how does she get access to a server?
Okay, it's open it's open server. So now diamond sits in the server having free cause with raging demon
Okay, it's on you since last night
Well, I saw I mean I I had just I just saw some of the messages like those were share or whatever between them work. It was like
Wow, it was pretty shocking. I mean, but it's like they
I guess I was here. Hey chair a couple months ago. I guess like I was like maybe a month ago
But I just saw him where he's like, you know, he's really into he's really into it. You know, I'm sure the best
Don't know why he gets mad if he's gay like just you know you gay man
But if the new it's almost like a new thing and now this like it's kind of like socially acceptable some
Little bit to like do that. You know, they don't do me something accepting communities of that
Gay got more rights than anybody, so it's the problem
Well, yeah, but that's the problem too is that you know, there's always like
There's always like a rebound reflect effect or whatever and it's like then it's like
There's gonna
The laws are always exist. For example, Trump's banned all the transgender from the military like again
It's like it's so for my active military service. And so I think maybe even the offices like which it was here
Let's do so it's like there's always going back and forth and I really don't think it's like a sexual
But you voted for Trump though
I didn't vote I didn't vote but my family my family's all Republicans though pretty much like
Yeah, I don't
Anybody anybody
Look just look at it psych how I'm not trying to bring politics to you
Thing right? Oh, we we wanted Trump out so we put Obama now because the bite it we want Trump back
That's what happens
We went back for what reason I mean, it's like invite. I mean by only just like, you know
Just really really an effective president even though it's like it wasn't that bad and I remember Trump
We got reading checks in the mail. We were getting you know, it was like a little bit of
Economic even though it was like, you know, the whole stuff was happening in the 2000 2001
21 to 2021
still it was like
Economically I was doing really well on my Etsy store and stuff, but
I don't know. I don't know how much to do with him or whatever
Yeah, I was reading readings. Hey, Kate. How are you?
Yeah, I was I sold like I did like 2000 readings on Etsy like in 2021 2022 like around that time like
Yeah, I was able to you know, then YouTube took off and then
Etsy is good. Let's say save you do like homemade stuff. Are you into art and you sell you do your own shit?
That's a good website. I'll buy a lot. I was just a homemade pet and pinch from there. Go ahead. Yeah, they're great
They have great stuff. It'd be great if you're into like if anybody's into like, you know
But you know in the occult or anything they have like really really great artists and search through like that make all kinds of
great stuff
But yeah, it's created everything
For people yeah people that make their own things and things like that crash people and
But they have that time at that time there were a lot of people getting like terrible readings
And so I was doing a really really well like I was and I had expensive readings to like because I had such a high demand
And I just I felt like just doing a certain amount of day
But yeah, but then once YouTube took off and that was before kind of like
There's all the video interface. I think so much of it was, you know, the open chats and stuff like that. So
Yeah, uh
Now it's perfect. You know, it's perfect. The time is well for youtube now. I'm so glad i'm here now
There was a god that uh, he did, you know the snow globes
Like yeah, but he had he did it like with in these cubes, but he made like the environment
I got a word with certain cards and I bought a whole lot of them shits
But you only get it from him like he only did it
I'm like people used to ask when they used to come to the crib, but you get there from I'm like, oh, I'm not saying nothing
It's a website. Yeah
Yeah, you can get really unique one-of-a-kind
Uh-huh things hand handmade things people, you know, it's like that's kind of rare in this world
Sometimes like to find it like you know all this like unless you're like out of like, you know
And she stores flea markets and stuff like that to find such a cool. I mean, it's just really cool. How I
Stuff from there. I was looking at when I was in a really into the fish hobby
I was looking at the website for different
tank designs
On the website people with
Plexiglass you could create different designs for fish tanks. Yeah
And it's more is more money, but you know, but it's crazy these eyes you can do with fish tanks
Yeah, I see to I see people on Etsy connect to tanks with a tool like so they could fish could go like travel through the two tanks issue
Mm-hmm. That's pretty cool. Mm-hmm. Yeah, I never had like the patience for fish. Like I would always like, you know, like
It's just hard to like keep I'm not good at keeping. It's hard. Yeah
You have to learn that you're gonna lose fish that's the heartbreak and in the fish hobby you're gonna lose fish
Well, yeah, man, they don't even live very long plus we get the fighters and stuff like that
You just it just
We learn I learned I learned that the whole you buy you if you buy once they say you like a certain fish
You buy multiple because you just never know because the fish could come sick
You got to treat the fish the water temperature can be fucked up something could go wrong
The feet are like the food so much shit could go wrong when you introduce a fish into a new environment
Just get it. It's good cat. You know, it's like it's a lot easier
They just eat shit yeah, yeah
Okay, I'm just putting a little pin about notice about the panel guys guys the panel is closed right now except like
You know, it's just me taking people one-on-one. I'd like to open it. There's instructions on the pin
There you go. I
Got fish now
Beta
Got fish now, but betas betas get a bad rap. You could keep betas together
You just got to make sure they got enough space enough plants. I had yeah, yeah in one take before
I didn't care if like a little like beta fish at my own like it was a three-year-old office
I was at and we had this little thing
I was like once a week I was like no like change the water and whatever and
That it smelled like worse than like human shit like when I would change that why it was just it smelled so bad
It's like it was one little fish. It was one of it. Hey, I'm making a tarot deck and
I did a tarot deck tarot cards today design and it said I said like I wanted to like beta and stuff
So what do you think?
Hey, I'll fuck with you. Wow. That's a young beater
Yeah, I'm with her cats
Yeah
Everybody you go do everybody. Yeah, I mean I'm gonna do you get a car for sure. Okay. That's yeah
Yeah, I mean I actually like even chat TPC suggested like they're like, why don't you do like a panel verse themed deck because that's like kind of like
That's your audience, you know, and so and then they would probably like to
Then I thought about it. They'd probably like to see their their self on a card, you know, it's like it's maybe all
Maybe I'll auction off a few for anybody to do. But I
Can I see if you don't yeah, I only I only have to I only this is my that's the third card
They're third card. I made but I have two other one. This is the full right there
There's the full that kind of like a beta there, too. You see like
That's the full and then
This is the magician here
Okay
Okay, but he has four fingers. I know someone noticed so so that's one one thing I have to
address, but it's interesting.
And Magician is the master of the mic, I don't know.
So it's making it like a, because when you talk to the chat
GPT, it remembers stuff now, so it knows all about my business
and it knows all about, you know, the channel and stuff.
And so they will tell me constantly referencing stuff
about the show into the deck and stuff like that.
So it was kind of interesting.
Some of the backstage they have a shirt that people put themselves without a shirt on.
I like that.
Looking good.
It's just a hang tight back there.
There's refreshments in the green room.
So, that's what I'm agreeing with.
Yeah.
The backstage it didn't fall.
Yeah, so yeah, it's actually the systems worked out pretty well too, you know
It's just like because I was having so many like just like the panels were just taking over where and it was like and then people were like
Just like taking up for granted like in this like
You know
There was another time consuming too and sometimes I didn't know what they were even talking about. So I was like it's like it's like
it's gonna take away from like me doing readings and stuff and
Or be focusing like unlike the audience and I want to make sure I'm
It's oh, you're I'm honest. You're gonna join lucky. We need to join. I
Have never met you. Have I?
She's real maybe I might have to make it I might get exception for low key because low key is never
Never been on the panel before. Let me look because what's an exception?
Yeah, yeah
Let me see. Are you my mod low key? Yes, you are my mod low key low key. Hey, bonas like this. She's got a wrench by her name
The honorary mod I gave away five memberships today. Congratulations to got them. I know the guy that uncle Jack
What was the guy's name? Uncle Jack or Uncle Joe?
Some uncle guy. I got it and then who else got one
I forgot but you know, I give away five I have over a hundred members now, so
That's pretty cool. That's a lot. Yeah, and
So everything's going good. I think I think if I'm in the right track things and
but they say
But you know, I know Q made a whole you made a whole show about me and it was said like it's called like oh
Send me money's it's like so it's also talk to you or something like that
And then he's like you know, I'm saying that this one's my message or whatever
Hey, give me give me money. I'll talk to you and then he's out to screw me sick sick this guy was he was he think he is?
Yeah, and then he's like
I should get paid every time he stutters and then he's accepted like look at the camera like angrily for like an hour
He's homeless. I've been told you when remember use dancer for him
Yeah, yeah, you had to use be submissive to her remember I said why you are you why?
Why are you jerking him off for what I must have been I must have been fucking drunk or something because I don't remember
You he's trying to bully you. Oh, that was all right. All right. That's the computer in him
Like they had me dance to the horse. Oh, no, no, no q was on it too. No q was doing making you and I'm like
Why you expect this homeless nigga?
Well, yeah, I had to do with it. He had nothing to do with it and you let this nigga
bozo you
I don't know. You know what the end they're the bozos because they're all the strikes
Well, I got what I got what I wanted they didn't give what they wanted everything
Yeah, fuck that. I told you that I said fuck. I've been
He begs for money. He's just a bum. He's just a bum sometimes people just beat bumps, right?
I mean he has the ability to have a show, he can like do longer shows, have canals,
he can like do other stuff, like he just like sits there staring at the camera, I didn't see
it, that's really all I saw. And then he talked to Joe Shipley for like five minutes, like
stuck each other's dicks off, and then it's like that was the show. I was like okay can you
plan about me, get out of the camera like it angrily, and then talk to Joe. That's his show?
No wonder it's like, I mean it's like
I know beer and drink 50 cent beer. Hey, sweet pea. I'm sub to you sweet pea
How you doing?
And then I don't know if you heard about Canada drive a Canada drive without like I don't want to say that
He was saying but he was saying like just terrible things about me
And then like I kicked him I'd like him off the panel a few times in the pinback stage
It was I didn't make him sit backstage. He decided to sit backstage. I can go for the panel
You know, it's like I don't care if you sit there people sit there all night if I don't want a month
But he was so mad that he like went and said like oh call the call the ASPC or like, you know, call like, you know
and look at troll on me and
And like all this other stuff and like making videos of me and stuff. So
Then he came back online and then well the DTM came back on like nothing happened then Christine told me like what he said
It was on be this show. I think that he was saying it and then
Then last night he I finally like to let him back up to like explain himself and
And it was like well, I was like you just you basically said it was mad or he didn't mean it or whatever
But I mean he says the fucking
But if he was so mean to me like I'm like I'm like a nice person
But I guess I've been pissed off about his perfect stage to I guess but it's like I really don't want to be on anybody's stage
I'm like I now that I have my own show. It's like I don't feel like you know, I need to
Sometimes I mean sometimes people tell you what's good, and then you just don't give a fuck my opinion
But you can take whatever you want to take
Sometimes don't go fuck. Well, I get how you are though. So that's how I say all right
It's like how he is and I'm back to fuck off. I'm not gonna keep repeating myself. I
Have to do that because yeah, it's like a real people like if I don't put says strong like
Boundaries on it said people like really like we'll say oh we own the show and there's like an old lap in your face
And then it's like other people see that and even when the mods will do that and it's like, okay
That's really like things are out of control, right? It's like the mods are putting you down
So it's like that is the bad look and so I've had to go, you know
Fix things around something even my trolls mods and stuff like that. I'm a nice person sometimes like
Like charisma Hernandez
Your shit is good. It's like when I come around. I like, you know me
I come around chill when the drama is drama the content content. I come around, but I
Just the fuck out. Hey, I box, you know, I back the fuck off
Like I got my own shit. I could you know, this other people shit. Are you filming? But hey, I don't one thing about me
I'm not a hater
You saw me. I'm not a hater. You do what you want to do. You got to get system
You do you what you want to do? I'll give you my penny on there
Hey, you take it or you want to drop it you I move on
Yeah, I mean, it's like and actually I do respect your opinion because you are like, you know
You're you're doing it. You're a successful person that was panels
Contact me we're colleagues and so I do take your I would take your opinion seriously
But so many people don't don't even have a show and trying to tell me what to do or tell me what's wrong
Even when people like yo, what's that man leeching off it's like
Yeah, I don't everybody panel psych. I don't anybody panel. Yeah, I'm I'm I'm Mr. Clipman
I don't need no help when I go live I go live. I don't I'm good
But I don't get it too. Go ahead. Okay, Casey's backstage. It's a if you don't and it's okay, so I don't know it easy
The panel's closed except for one-on-one. He should pay he should yeah
So yeah, if you want to sponsor the panel for a few hours, I'll be open panel for everybody
I mean, it's not it's not like it's not trying to disrespect you or anything. I'm just saying like
Yeah, he got no he got he never get he never stays no content
No, nothing people like that should pay KZ. Go pay pay KZ mumbles all the time
Please pay for you. You don't add no context as nothing
He's just like uh, it's like he's one of those guests that it was me. Yeah. Oh, I won't say much anything bad
It's like, you know, you don't have to say not to say yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah
Keep it loose. I don't know what I don't know what it's a I can read with if you don't on his like little
I don't know if it was it was you start turning or you say it was like, you know
We're gonna say if you don't want me here. I'll leave or something like that, but I don't know you as events. So
Just want to say you have a system you can read the pin comment about it, but I'll keep putting my you know
You can sit next stage if you want people can you know is like if you want to be yet
Just wait for your turn. I'll do a one-on-one. Yeah, I hope also my spliff is gone. I'm about to be I'm smoking
You show me I'm smoking my split. I hop over my split is gone
Per least so you might be laughing like it's funny, but already I've had like ten ten panels sponsored in a few days
And so it's like it's not that I'm you know
I
Will that's what I said for somebody paste and now you can go in together
You guys can say one dollar piece and then I'll open the panel right or you can say two people can say five dollars
And I'll still play now. It'll be advertising because I put it in the banner, right?
Yeah, you have a nice old site.
I know, but people say, oh, well, it's open for everyone.
I'm trying to tell you, no, I'm not
going to be opening for everyone unless I'm holding
the panel hostage for quality.
I'm holding a hostage so that it's
a better, safer place for everybody.
KZ that is my system. I have to stick by my system. Okay, it's not that I don't want you up here
I'll talk to you after Sam and just come up here wait your turn. I mean come on
We tell him alone and then you come up
I'll talk to anybody one-on-one. Thank you Casey. He look let him let him get mad Casey throw at nothing
Yeah, at least I will
I don't know. I I will wait your turn Papas. We got it. You go get your turn
If I'm gonna have people coming if I'm gonna have a group of people because people people change around other people right when they
Think if someone's trying to impress page or something like that or like something like that
They'll try to like, you know, so try to maybe you know, or you're already girl, right?
The people just want to impress people when there's other people there
And I'm not saying this is that I'm not explaining the system. I'm saying is that
Oh yeah, well, I'm just gonna say my thought process behind it is like that if I'm it's like I'm not gonna like
Be like like have all these groups of people just overwhelm me and like it lets them like to run free like some people have been thinking
Like and so if like you don't want to if you don't want to do open piano
You don't have to or just wait for somebody who says concert and then come on
Other than that you should be here like maybe to watch me a little bit. Hopefully sometimes
I leave sometimes
Well, I just watch to see the chat and doesn't chat miss me if I might just like you know about there
Maybe one or two people let him go
Let him go and Jimmy when Jimmy go live KZ. You can top on that panel so I could cook you over there
That's gonna be a good example. You feel me. Okay. You figure
And KZ it's like
I don't think you understand it. He doesn't understand any system. He thinks don't push and have the balls the balls are
I'm gonna say it's sick for my system. And so, you know
Look now you're trying to attack you see how funny he is look see I'm telling you whoa little pear tethers
I'll be your look
When you tell me about your system the first time I got on your panel
You said alright one-on-one. Somebody's be on somebody's behind me. He said alright, Samman
You're time to go. I stopped off. I stepped the fuck off. Fuck. I'm arguing about
Okay
Okay, so anyway
So but I can't make it. I'm gonna make an exception right now. There's an exception. I'll make it right now
Yeah, for page is good page. You'll always be essential
Yeah, because you know
pages
Page is a wonderful
wonderful colleague
How is that we're just having a chat nothing bad like your kids is kind of mad because he was backstage and I was
I didn't know there was something
No, no, no, you're fine. You're fine. Nothing's going on. It's okay. Well, yeah, how are you today?
All right, how are you good?
You saw the new yeah, I made the new intro. I don't know if you saw that
Okay, here we go here we go this is the new
Intro or I'll play it on the exit here we go
from the shadows of the sub conscious to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls this is psyche
awakens crowd whoosh sparkly chimes thundercrack
you smooth mystical yo welcome to the madness buckle in tight tear it on deck third ion
flight truce get told he goes unfold we stir the soul with a tea surf cold panels be popped
Trolls be dropping Spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard Tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marbles fan from above It's like the Awake has stepped in the flame
We call you truth, we say your name It's wild, it's real, it's so deeply played
Now grab your tea and slay the dead It's like the Awake has don't look away
Your shadow's talkin', it came to stay We laugh, we cry, we speak, we scream
Did you like pause it or something?
That's pretty fucking cool.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Yeah.
Yeah, I uh...
That means pretty cool AI software and then I had I had somebody on the show earlier
I think I mean another program I can use and so I'm gonna hopefully make some other ones for my other videos
This is expensive the last two I made the ones Alex one down stage one and this one we're like 50 bucks
I think Mike Mike is
You good
Hello, they're working. Yeah, better. Yeah, better. Better.
Alex is the country song the whatever page we fall in love with me. That's a fucking hit. So just we do you wait
off that one out here
That song for the show that you just played is like I like that the it's kind of mellow and it's masculine rather than feminine
Huh? I just like you. Thank you so much. Yeah, and I live it, huh?
Yeah, what do you think about the page of the page in the video though that in your video? I think she looks
Similar. Oh, you did it. Okay. You see the video. Oh my gosh
You're talking you see the screen. Yeah, no, you have to do the video. I can see okay
Have you seen the video Sam here? Yeah, I've seen the video. I thought okay. Well, we're playing again. Oh good
There we go
The Alex walks the beat in the city light, flashing blues under New York nights.
But his heart's up north where the rivers run free with the blonde hair, beauty from April Country.
He's got a badge of dream and a thing for a laugh, caught a glimpse of her smile.
show he's thinking real deep page are you the one i've been missing in my sleep
He's eating steak, somewhere in the middle they both take a break
He'd trade his knife stick for a fishing pole
Chase her laughter like it's his patrol
Oh Paige, don't you know you're the catch of the day
And this cop's got one hell of a line to say
Wild pigs got a beard
That supposed to be me, Paige. That supposed to be me. That supposed to be me. That supposed to be me.
Who is that there's a Peter Pan character running around to see he's hiding in the bushes earlier in the video
You can see him for a second when it's like he's like he's like he's what he doesn't he's obsessed with page now
He's just watching them and he wants he's like the Cupid. He wants them to be together forever
Five o'clock shadow should full beard
Okay, there's a little weird things in AI like if you look at the print like where it's like it's the words
It's like not the right words and it's like um, if there's a fish like going through the air
There's like really
Fishing pole the cars are jumping backwards. I mean, there's like little things that are wrong
They may be a perfect but it's like you know, just take up a story your head
and like but she started out way way way hotter than me and then
Okay, I basically didn't watch it until it was I play on the show
She had no glasses
It was a kind of a good it was like kind of a I think it your smile a little bit page. Did my glasses stand man?
I got the Dahmer glasses. Yeah
What you try to say try to look for an already, huh?
The beef sector name me Jeffrey Dahmer when I first started going in there last year they were like they call me Jeffrey Dahmer
Like you have the glasses, huh?
So they call me, so they put in my little like streamer,
I think they put Jeffery, like I'm like the good pussy.
You know who the good pussy is?
And you think good pussy, she's in Texas.
Yeah, she's like a, kind of like the Mothry,
deep sector kind of area, but she's pretty cool.
Like she has big panels, like, but it's like, you know,
it's all black people and I've been on the,
I played Jeffery on somebody's tail.
I lost, but I got some points.
I think it was your mic.
It's not my mic, it's not, it's not, I'll go mute.
Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Look, see? No feedback.
Hello? Hello? See?
It is you. Me? No, no, it's not you, it's Sykes.
There, is that better?
No, I said, why you took your glasses off? I'll talk about the
To see if it worked did I put in the back on I have to see
No, oh you blind blind. No, I'm not blind blind
But like I can't read that tiny writing and like a fucking screens mess my eyes up. I don't know what it is
But you know where contacts?
No, I don't like them
Freaks me out sticking my finger in my eyeball
Not supposed to touch them
It's gross anyway. No, I fucking I don't like my contacts at all and
My friend got contacts like to her and her brother
I don't know what the hell they were thinking they thought they didn't have to take their contacts out
And so they just kept like putting more and more contacts in thinking they were dissolvable
Mm-hmm. Oh, there was like I watched them pull out a million contacts. I'm just
There you can't put stuff in your eyes like that. It's gross
But if it works for you, it does it works, right?
I used to wear contact different color contacts just to change my color though, you know in high school
Have you seen clockwork orange clockwork orange? Have you seen that anybody?
Tropical orange. It's called clockwork orange. It's Stanley Kubrick movie
It's really interesting. It takes place in the future and it's kind of about it said England and it's about this guy kind of like a gang
I'm like these like they're kind of like these bullies or whatever and he's a criminal and he does something really really bad one night
You get you get arrested they offer him a program where they can they do an experiment on him in order to get like out of jail
And like a like a lesson a year
But I won't give too much away, but the experiment entails they like they like open his eyes with like little clips
So he can't close his eyes
And they make him watch this like horrific like all these all this like violence and stuff on tv until you become as like
It's sickened by it and then they desense it so it's a really interesting movie
It's a
Yeah clockwork orange. Yeah. Yep. It's mk ultra. It's about mk ultra. Yeah
Is that mk ultra?
Ivana see pee and mermaid. Well, there's a lot of people in here fishy fingers
Stay turned Jamie everybody in the whole everybody's here. Okay. Gotty. They did they hate on your positivity
Always positive
They don't all hate it just some it's okay, that's their
Purgatory fine change them out change
I'm not nice all the time
She's not I can I I can attest to that world. It's hard to stay positive all the time. That'd be psycho
Right. Well, yeah, because that's not
Nobody's nobody's happy all the time. That's kind of scary
I fucking there's just a bunch of creeps there. There's not enough mods. It was actually made it happen made it work
But anyways, I would just get so I just one chance you get to play around
You just fucking get out of here and I'm explain why and then that would be it and then leave and then everybody else started doing it
You know, it actually worked out really well. We weeded it out all them
Most of the blue what do you call them? I'm gonna come lose patrols. I guess uh-huh
Well, I mean, you know, I know like I should maybe I should not say her name
But I really maybe what you would uh because Emma is just like, you know, she's kind of like the
That kind of sexy figure and she got so much of the sexual trolling and and other trolling and stuff like that
Like she like a really the way she handles her chat is like pretty pretty good if you ever like to subserv like she's like
She's 25,000 subscribers like a if she is like she has a lot of mods too, but we
I was there last night I was watching I just I don't say anything. I don't say anything because I was like I don't want to like
Say, I don't want to do your 101, you all right?
OK.
Thank you, Samman.
Bye, Samman.
That's what you say.
God bless, man.
Mr. Fine.
Bickering.
This is like, I don't know, people drink tea and fight.
I'm so baked, man.
I had a shower.
I thought I was going to go out to visit some people,
and then I thought we were going to go golfing,
and it started raining.
And now I'm just stoned out of my tree,
and I'm glad I don't have to drive.
Like 10 gravel roads to go somewhere.
But I'm really I'm gonna make food right now. I don't think I can make like poverty pass them
I'll just drink probably
Let's drink. I have some uh, I see some my Swiss limonades or my car limonades. I don't know twisted cheese. I put some tea
The ladies in the chat would love these if they haven't already had them and you know what?
You're good like me. You'll like this drink. I promise I have good taste and poos
They're good. I have I try them. There's the bomb. They uh
they haven't
Is that a popular brand over there for for the regular drink because they know that
The the Arizona I see because that's what they were
Not for liquor. It's usually like fucking those stupid twisted teas or like vintage teas or
Yeah, well those those are brand new because of the Arizona they're known for like having the dollar drinks
They've won dollar big ice teeth that size, but now they had of the hard ones
Yeah, yeah, yeah, the alcohol is expensive, but they're regular drinks of cheap
Well, there you go expensive here they come in these like little tiny fucking packs. There's only six of them and they're like
Like 20 some 12 over 24 bucks. I think they're 20
They're a lot
So got into it every drop. I guess
You said autograph oh
You had your race or rain use race or rain actually has a clockwork orange blu-ray
And if she had an autograph blu-ray collect clockwork orange DVD
So Stanley Cooper is the guy that he directed The Shining and Eyes Wide Shut and Space Odyssey
2001 I think.
And so he's very quite a famous director.
He's even suspected of directing the moon landing, right?
You know how there's like people said, oh, it may have been filmed on a stage or whatever.
And so he could have done that like and then and if you watch this shining a little kid in the shining has that Apollo 11
sweatshirt on which is like the moon ship that should the tix of the moon
So it's kind of interesting like there's like little signs
Okay, I'm going to go to Pap's coin. I
Couldn't decide what started this one in the shower and then open this one after this is colder. Here we are
Is that can you do shower beer?
Well, what is that when you like?
Promise I'm gonna write
No, we drink beer in the shower and cold beer in the shower. It's amazing
Really does it every single person?
I kind of think I've ever heard I don't know. Yeah, you really do you drink them in the bath or just the shower?
Bath and shower, okay
Nice cold one. Yeah, see that's
The song got it so right it's like, you know, you like I told I told a song all about you
I told I told I mean I told AI all about you. That's how they knew
Exactly what to say, but uh, yeah, like I said, I said she likes to hunt fish and drink beer
I have to say I told about you. I do it's like it just ran with it. It just ran with it. It ran with it
Yeah, I sometimes can find myself if I'm on other chats, you know, especially, you know, because you're, you know
You're you're getting started by your feet. I'm a distraction
I'm a distraction sometimes in chats and it's like I don't want like to distract away from you
That's why I was quiet, but I did I did I did stop by and watch and I'm very impressed
Thanks, and no, you're people love you. You're gonna do really well. I mean if you want to do this like
You can do this like you're gonna you can have you're gonna track the audience like for sure
You're gonna have like more people than you could like beat off with with the stick, right?
And so it's like you have to you know, just ease into it
I would say like that's why I just take it really slowly
Going in just take it take it very easy on
Bringing people up on the panel if you ever do just take it easy on that or and then don't let them get to you
They're gonna say
What's that?
It's why I just only use the panel one time like I don't want to honestly do it without like yeah
I don't want to do it to organize it beforehand with the other readers and stuff like you can have somebody
It's just a guest on with it
Like we'll just like tell like stories or do you fucking paranormal shit or something stupid
I don't want to do that because at least I can pay attention that way because if I'm tapped in then I can't pay attention
And to do all the stuff that I need to do if people be waiting backstage stuff would be going on
It would just be it's probably too much. Yeah, yeah, I need to just do the lives the way I do
As if you're talking to yourself, you're really talking to the chat, but whatever.
There's so much you're up to.
Great.
Well, yeah.
And it is, you are talking to yourself, but you see yourself on the screen, and so it's
like, it's kind of like looking in a mirror when you're like streaming to yourself, and
then you're being looked at too.
You can you will
Really like be successful. I feel like you know, I feel like I just see the signs like I'm there's people that just have a really
Great feeling about you like a really good. You know, I think that you just you have the whole package
You know, it's like, you know, you you're talented
you're funny smart
and beautiful and
Salty a little bit
Little salty little sweet, right?
So but I think you know, I think you have a wide appeal, you know, and I hope I hope I think you'll help a lot of people and
You know, I wish you really the best best best time doing that. So I'm really proud of you
I'm not leaving but I know if it's like I feel like you might I hope I hope you don't leave me, but it's like I
I would but I feel like you know eventually like it look when I was on Emma's
I was her mod right for like months and stuff and I had my channel, but I didn't do any shows
I would just be in her show and I was like I was just so and then
Then she finally like fired me and told me that they fucking never talked to her again
As a mod yeah, she fired me as a mom
No, cuz I was we had a we had like a we were like talking on discord
Like we were like her I talked on the phone many times and stuff like like we were pretty like I was her mod
I was one of her first mods. I was our first member in her chat since you when she moved over to YouTube and stuff
I made a joke one night. I said I had a hundred thousand subscribers
We're gonna have a
Baby oil slip-and-slide or something on a ditty party or something and then she got then she wrote me an email and like
It's like, oh, she's like, you're accusing me
of doing these horrible things like Diddy did.
And I was like, this is a joke.
I was just like a good nature of joke.
But then she got really mad about that.
And then she did an interview with me.
And that was my first interview.
And then we had a falling out after that.
She'd maybe take the interview down.
But.
Yeah, it was uh, it still it still hurts because it was like we were it was like we were so close like
Maybe we weren't close
Well, it's close to the I could I could be
I would have been very loyal to her but drop the link. We have we can't have people on the panel right now
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
And it's a sponsorship because it will be
Let's go. Oh, we can't sit it because it'll have the same
Yeah, I can I can
I'm gonna do it later. Well, I like it and it and I'll also put the banner up
And I'll put your the name of your channel in the banner and so it is a sponsorship
And it's like and then you know, hopefully people will like
They'll behave because you know you can see your sponsor in the panel and so they'll behave a little better. Hopefully
Do you want to do it now? I can do it on credit or
I trust you. I know you're good for it
Okay, we actually have to yeah, we have we have two panels
Oh, okay. Well, I don't care. So just ones that have a question. Do we have
Dave did you have to put in PayPal?
Yeah, you can use PayPal
And then we have so okay, should I put my PayPal backstage? I'll put it back safe. Yeah, probably
God I do have such a big forehead, bro. I'm so annoying
Oh, I mean, look at my, look at my, plus I have to say, you know, you see my, I literally
get called caveman and Neanderthal by like, people in chat, not everybody, not everybody,
but, but even the Neanderthals were not necessarily like, not intelligent.
We actually were so related to the man was all they bread with us some of them did and so we have some of it
So they were also artistic
Casey you can just yell yourself all day, you know just yell in the chat. That's that's that's the echo chamber
You know the chat to see how much the chat cares, okay?
Yeah, Sebastian
God, he jokes about Egonian wildfire.
Well, that's how that were funny.
Justin, that wouldn't be funny.
No jokes about fires.
It's truth, I care.
Here's how much I care.
Zero.
KZ.
I read it because I just read the chat. I mean, when are you gonna get your psyche? What do you mean, Sweet Pea?
Real release now. I think they, I don't know. They're pretty, uh...
You really know what's on there.
They're talking about release. They're just chats going all over the place.
Does it have to have the heart?
Oh, no, no the hard stuff part of it. That's just that's that's that's for you the heart starts for you
Oh, that's cute. No, I had to ask cuz I'm like
I don't think I should just smoke that if you ever do smoke weed
This good
Here, I'll just say it. It's
454 and
I don't know what it's called
454. Oh, yeah
Spunky is asking if you've made your Amazon wishlist yet.
No, I didn't do it yet. I'm such a procrastinator and I don't have you know how to do a page. You know how to do it
Okay, so on the on the product page, it's gonna it's really hard. It's kind of hard to find it will say add to list
There'll be like a little option. It will say add to list. You just like scroll down to see add to list
It's gonna be the near the price of it and everything and then you can create and you have to make a wishlist
You make it make sure you go in the settings to make it a public or not a public wishlist
But they share with the person
You have to share your address with or you don't have to share your address but you have to set it up so you put your address in there and they can send it to you so they don't know not to share your address with anybody so it's pretty easy and then you make sure it's a public list and then share the URL I'll help you if you
I'll get the banner ready for you. Prairie page wins and wildflowers?
Prairie wins and wildflowers.
Okay.
Or Prairie page is fine too.
I don't care.
But the channel is called Prairie wins and wildflowers?
Wildflowers, spiritual arts.
I'm gonna fix that. It's too long, by the way.
Okay.
Okay, did I do it?
Yes, there's your cute little face. I found you
Prairie wins version spiritual arts. Yeah, okay. Yeah
Sheesh
Oh, yeah, there's a little conversion in Canada. It's okay. It's just fucking
It's aggressive
If there's if there's if there's a if there's a big fee to just take a couple take a couple bucks off for I'm fine
I'm good
Spiritual wins and arcs. Okay. I have to pick what type payment type for goods and services or family and friends
You can say friend
And let's see is it 8 so until 11 p.m.
Good time time
Hey
And
Now just as bad as everybody else
Okay, guys, I'm gonna put the link for the chat up you guys are welcome to join page and I
And oh here you go. Thank you page. There's the banner
And you get to pick the color too. What kind of what color would you like the banner to be?
Not this one
Okay, so what color?
purple or like
And maybe that's my favorite color, but if it's
This one purple or the other one. Maybe try the other one. Yeah, purple purple
The darker the darker
It doesn't make sense.
Right there?
Later.
No.
Darker or lighter?
No, like brighter. That's good. That's fine.
Okay, brighter.
That'll do.
Okay.
That's good. I'm on the future.
Okay, perfect.
Okay, don't let Sebastian have the creeps on page and it's gross. Okay
Yeah, if you have any advice about the panelist guys, just let me know Goddy Goddy knows what it's talking about
Okay, Justin's gonna come up in 10 minutes. Awesome. The darker was the better. It's okay. It's just the the banner
It looks purple looks good on you. I'm getting some new new new shirts to from team team has like really
Cheap shirts. I mean not cheap and it's bad, but like inexpensive. They're like
$5 shirts and then it's like probably $3 shipping
So a $8 for t-shirt like a really nice thick design shirts, right? So it's like
Nowadays they charge like $25 for those. I'm not ignoring you sweepy. Okay, okay
Sweepies in the chat
Do winners there and Cali and
And Cal in Los Angeles, it does not snow, but it snows in the mountains nearby
I think we have like some mountains nearby where it snows and it's like higher elevation, but LA is just always warm
Okay, okay, so sweet people like a reading
No, I think she was I think she was asking she was I think she was asking you though, so I'm gonna try to
Oh, yeah, I know I thought about asking the reading when she asked for the reading. I thought she was asking for a page. I think she said it can page read me. I'm sorry. I didn't mention it. Okay.
I'll just do a reading on my channel later, because everyone gets kind of annoyed when I fucking read. I don't want to get fished out of here.
Okay. Would you like a reading page? I have like five new decks. I have the Cat deck, the Alien deck. Which one would you like? Cat, Alien, Van Gogh, or the Monster?
Okay, these alien cards, these cards are kind of, kind of smaller cards, the cards on,
on Teamu are kind of smaller cards and they don't have a manual, but they're like, they
feel really good in the hands and they're like, you know, they're, they're nice to them.
Oh, when it popped out, made a flyer.
Yeah.
Okay, well we had a flyer we had a flyer last time too, so I'll just say I'll read you the flyer and the flyer is this two
of pentacles and so this is like but this two of pentacles is
You know two pentacles about keeping things balanced. This one looks a lot like
Your reflection of the aliens reflection, you know, it's like better. It's like
And so I think you're finding this balance within yourself.
Also looks like he has these cards in his hand too.
Like does he have, they're carrying cards like, right?
And so it also means maybe it's like different ways
people can take the same person.
Okay.
So what do we have?
We have the world card.
And so you've completely completed a successful cycle.
It may have been hard and everything,
but at the end of the cycle,
you're coming out and having a new cycle begin.
the old stuff fall away which is good right and we have temperance and so this is like just
staying balanced and being able to continue to stay balanced and also this is oh yeah it looks like
this one has like a little like you know he's like sitting with the like an angel and an alien
kind of like having a coffee or they have the the angel alien bringing them together but I'd say you
both the cards are balanced, especially the two of Pentacles.
Maintaining the balance, even those things may be topsy-turvy sometimes.
Ooh, look at this, the sun.
That's a beautiful sun.
I love to see that. It's really cool.
We know the sun is the most positive card in the deck.
It means all good things.
If there's been darkness and everything,
it's like you're just coming out of it.
You're starting a new cycle.
It's like, remember, it's like, it's a new start.
I've been, I've been, I've actually been good.
Now we have nine of cups.
So nine of cups is like, you know,
you're just guard your happiness.
It's like, he's like sitting there like.
But like, I haven't been like crying or anything,
Steve, but anymore.
Oh yeah.
Well, yeah, but I mean, it's like,
there's so much good things to come.
I thought it, I just didn't step in it.
And so I'm just like stoked for the new shit to come.
Yeah, that's yeah, and I'm not trying to like say anything
And then I think they're all have these little cups right there all these this nine
It's like the nine is they're usually a guarding a guarding the cups and everything this feels like they're kind of like sharing
It's like kind of like kind of looks like oh and a cups, too
Like it gives us different things in each of them. Yeah. Yeah
And so maybe like there's yeah, which and also which is like the seven of cups maybe like a lot of different
Ways to look at something or options or something like that
And so but I would also say the traditionally nine of nine of cups is like, you know kind of
Guarding your happiness and like you about you, but you have all the cups behind you're like
Yeah, yeah, exactly
Yeah, like so there we go. So sometimes that's a good good thing. Hey traveling gypsies here. Hey, what's up?
Hi guys, good seeing you guys
Sebastian do not be perverted please
Sebastian he's like asking me about feet. He's like show your feet
No, I'll show you I'll show you mine Sebastian. All you need is my feet and then nobody wants to see my feet
They're big somebody's paid for feet like I don't understand what's it's like people have a fetish a fetish
I know but like what a five bucks a fucking toe
No, sometimes more sometimes more there's actually no people can you ever see the king of the hill episode where Peggy like she has like
She has like really large feet like it turns out she has like she buys like women's like size 10 or 11 or something
And like she has these huge features really embarrassed of it
But then it's like she figures out like that on the internet
They're gonna they could they pay for foot fetish photos if you get some this website where the
It's like a Peggy's feet and she doesn't really understand that people are you know
Have a fetish for it and something that she was thought of as a a pro foot website
Approved for a website. Yeah, but I have size 13 feet. I have a big old feet. So
I have size I don't even mind you're like hooves. They're not even feet. They're so small
No, they're like five and a half
six maybe six
I could buy kids to use as I am for half price. It's dope
Like the kids versions are so much cheaper
nice
That's like imagine me like like a lot of dwarves that can only like shop in the children's section and stuff like that
that'd be kind of like a
Probably the powers like a dwarf that really like dress up sexy. I might not like that, but you know
Oh, yeah, but the little the little what are the little the little dwarfs girls like the little little women or something?
Yeah, something little women
They're cooking they scrap and everything all the time. Oh, yeah, and they're like running clubs and like fucking
But they're funny when they fight they
You gotta write up like
It's cute and then there's these two dancers like there's these twin sisters or there were sisters or something and they were like
It was called what were the names it was called like some kind of ratchet name and
But yeah, and they were they would they would come out and twerk there's these two little twins
They would come out and twerk just for and that's all they do just come and twerk to the music and everyone just goes wild
I mean this kind of like
I can't remember them either. I've just seen this stupid real thing the other day
How about the the more how about the Mormon? Did you ever watch that the sister wives? Yeah, yeah, you're listening up easy
Hi easy
Easy you're on the show. Yeah, so
They're gonna have it in my tripod page. It's all bad. I tried to tape it back on
Yeah, and so now I'm using this thing right here, I got
For like seven bucks
I'll try to fix it. Hold on. Let's see once again. Oh, yeah
You saw the glasses page you like them
Yeah, they look great.
Thank you so much.
I'm just hating on my side to them.
I mean, I do think I do like these, though.
Still, I might keep these, I think.
Like, I do like, yeah, I'd like these, too.
I'm gonna keep these, too.
You look like a few different people.
Now, three different people.
Like, he just, he gets a disguise.
Those ones, like, you're probably not walking
near, like, families and children and stuff.
I know, these kind of look weird.
Yeah, I know, these kind of look-
Like, you can probably just wear them, like, at home
or, like, on the other side of the sidewalks, or whatever.
I will, I will, I will, I don't.
I don't need to wear these unless I'm reading and I don't need to read unless I'm really on the computer
It's a tablet because my tablet has the tiniest little writing like it is like millimeter tall
It's like it's like so tight. I can't even believe I can read it now, but it there's pocket sand. Why are you blood?
Oh sweepy sweepy
You want to read him from me sweepy because page says she's gonna do her on her show later
give one i just don't want to take up the fucking just do it do it people come here for
specific psych and match it's not one of them yes it is they come here for you specifically
i think people people love you seriously but do you mind have a like a collective or or would
you like uh you know maybe i'll pull a card for somebody and i don't care i guess it's
You don't mind that's awesome. I'm just trying to figure out which are you know what check these out
Huh, so I got these I haven't used them ever. I did the I did last night, but
They're like the self-care sacred oracle and I thought that they were kind of lame and then I actually opened the box
It looked at them because I've had them for a long time
I just got like a bunch of them on time from somebody second hand and
It's like
Look at these
I think it looks like a delet card. Oh, I love it. Yeah, that's a nice car page
Look at the fairy one just peeking in the darkness. I love the uh, I love the aesthetic
Oh, we have another guest hold on Jade. Oh, so this is gonna be so Canada dry. You know, you are banned until
Tomorrow night because he was banned by somebody and because he was talking shit about me and then he was like
Then he was talking when he was like defending himself last night and then the first somebody got tired from defending himself and
for 24 hours
Well, okay, okay page. He was saying that really disgusting things like disgusting things about me
He said he's saying call the animal control on me and stuff like that. Okay, so
Yeah, it's a little far far. Yeah, a little bit far a little far. Yeah a bit far fetched. I think
So I would say you know, he's my buddy bringing back up, but that's not cool. So I
Mean and I will bring him back after
Because I know and I for and I told him I forgive him and I do forgive
I'm not mad. I'm not mad. No shade. I forgive you. I'll have you on again, but you know
Yeah, and it wasn't me that banned you. It was somebody donated for it.
Hey, Kiti, do you want to pick the cards that I start with for the collective?
There's somebody to do the...
Just pick a card page. I'm watching, but I got bad service for somebody then.
Ooh, I just smashed that.
Mm-hmm.
High psyche, high page, if you like to hit me.
Here's one, I guess. It's lean, but it's fine about it.
Well, I have one in the city service all the time, so it's kind of refreshing. That's not me
The odds right page gods, I'm always that clear service
Yeah, I don't I always people are always thinking about it. Why are you even a streamer if you can't stream like fucking try
I've never had good service though.
I'm just going to back out because I heard myself on the TV and I sound terrible.
I love you, Zee. Thank you. See you soon.
Hi.
This is cute.
Family.
Live the longest arms in the planet
Okay
So the mantra is I share unconditional love and receive it in return
So peaceful relations with your family whether biological
Adoptive or chosen are incredibly important this time families can offer a sense of unconditional love and be there for you in times of need
You're being called to tune in to your energy of unconditional love many of us or unresolved family of traumas as this is a
Oh, is this past as we evolve our perspective perspective? Holy shit. There's no periods here. We can find forgiveness in our hearts
We eventually realize that our families are always
Have always done but the best they could with the resources level of emotional development and acknowledgement they had at the time
So tap into your divine motherly nature as you practice forgiveness and unconditional
love.
Look for opportunities to heal any old wounds with family members and find ways to connect
with them.
Whether it's tough or through a phone call, sharing a meal or planning a visit, if connecting
directly is not possible then try finding peace through meditation and by setting up
intention to transform any negativity into feelings of love.
Beautiful.
And it said the same thing over and over again.
It likes that message.
Yeah, it was a nice message actually.
Kind of just a reminder to like call the ones that are still alive, you know?
Or like that you maybe need to make a link with.
Yeah.
I really, I feel that because I used to talk to my grandmother all the time when I was, you know, growing up and then like
it's never called like the last 10 years and it's like
I'm sure she would have probably like to hear from you more and so always regret. So instead of having regrets try to
Remember just call your call your parents call your while you bother while we have them, right?
I can't remember if somebody told me on the panel to just do this with my cards, these specific ones.
I think it was maybe, I don't know if it was LV or Ziggy, but I finally did it and it's freeing. It's so freeing.
Oh yeah, that method. The spread, the spread.
Well they need, they're hard to shuffle like, so you need to just do it, just get down and do it.
Well, I try but maybe try some of the team ejects you have to get the get the ones from China that they said they're like
They're like only like five bucks and everything
But they're all the same size and stuff and they're just like really they're really small and really easy to shuffle for me
I mean, it's like I'm able to shuffle them like I'm not that great at shuffling and you're so you'll have no problem
They're just like really like like the Santa mute a
Mm-hmm. I have that one that I got from fucking
I think it was wish or Aliexpress back when we used that and it's kind of the same quality as you know
So it didn't come with a book, but it came just the cards are a nice size
They're pretty much like for a good hand
Because some of these are fucking insane like look at it. Hold on these ones
Where'd they go?
Okay, and these ones aren't even the other ones, like I got my grandma a set, well I got them for me and they were like this long, and this skinny, but I don't have them to show you, but look at these ones, these are even more awkward, like to do anything with, you can't hold them very good, they don't, they stick together, yeah, it's a whole thing, but.
Look at these, it's like, so I bought two decks of cards, one was like the Cocaine Tarot, and it's, um,
pretty thin. I paid a lot of money for it and got it a long time ago.
But it's like, they're like this, and same with these ones. So they came with a nice box and everything, the Joyseeker.
But they're like paper thin, and just bend them.
It's shitty.
So anyways, I wonder if you could like laminate them.
Oh, yeah, I mean, oh, oh, did you see my my cards that I make I'm making a deck, you know with the through AI
So I have a few cards already. So here's
So this is the fool
On the screen
Take out the screen
See it. No, it's not. Oh, there is. Oh, that's good. That's great. Okay. I love that
It's very like it's very psyche and wonderland
And then this is the magician
Okay, and you want to see the empress
I mean, they said for some reason they the empress next is in the high priestess
But yeah, it should be the high priestess, but they put the empress here's the empress
Nice
It's like a different completely different own and like it's not busy. It's kind of nice. It's it's offsets it a little bit
Right to look at
Yeah, I think it might have a little bit of a because it is with AI
But yeah, I put up I said make it look like beta and it did that amazing. Yeah, that's wicked. I love it
It's the cat that's the tuxedo cats. Oh my god. I thought it was just the holes in that are like the tear arms. Holy shit
Their cats
Oh my god, did you show beta? Oh
Not yeah, I haven't seen her yet. So
There you go
Beautiful. Thank you. Thank you so much. I mean yeah, the AI is
Remember what I tell it about my show and stuff and so it's like it constantly is referencing stuff and I like asking
It was it was it was telling me it's like, oh, do you want to do it?
Do you want to do a terror Dexa and you should make one? I was like, oh my gosh, so it's like kind of like a
Honestly, I've made a bunch like and made or whatever, but I don't I really this day
I'm gonna try the AI one because this is all does it for you. Did you print it off or something?
Um chat gpt. Yeah, it'll make it for you. I'll do the image for you
It will for free
I think you can do a couple of few images for you a day and then it's like you just tell it you want to
But I would say talk to it a little bit like tell it like about you do you do a tarot business or like tell about what you
Wanted to know a bit here from Canada and you like to do this and this you don't remember these little things and it will
Incorporate that in the deck
Yeah, talk to it like talk to it like it's a person like I that's what I do. I like I'm conversational
wow look at unique this is a weed thing this is a weed i got it like the one of the first weed
dispensary is the one like pano by panorama in vernier bc okay so anyway it's just uniqueness
and i used to have snaziness and i used to have happiness and then there was another one but i gave
them away for like christmas presents and cards and i kept this one it looks like a tarot card doesn't
Those are cool. I love the the Geometrics and stuff. Yeah, yeah, the busy be busy deck. Anyway, oh
I'm so tired now
I'm thinking about getting some coffee. I think that's I had the best coffees. I'm thinking about getting them again
It's one was a like a salted caramel
Salted caramel latte and then one of them was banana and it's like a Vietnamese coffees. I think they're very very good
Banana coffee, I've never had banana coffee. It was so good like banana and
banana and
Brown sugar isn't it?
Let's see just
What are you trying to say Justin? That's banned. I mean it's like if it's banned then it maybe you
She thinks twice about saying it
I have banned words, you know, it's like a bit. So if you also have a filter on my chat
So if it does like, you know, some things are if you know, there's usually only if there's like bad language or something
Or too many emojis
He's such a cute baby.
Tricks is up here.
Hi Tricks.
He's got like people or the camera.
Okay baby go.
Ouch!
Your back feet are like a little rooster talisman.
Tricks always has lots to say like rave and hay.
Good morning.
So long
He's a per like he'll sit like when you lay don't you
So the cat's purr is so healing
Master 2025
Don't you think it's like it's some kind of magical frequency? I think it must be like it's like yeah
they say it's on that the
The god frequency the light freak hi Christine. Hey spunky
Lou Lou Nancy everybody's here everybody. Yeah, there's a lot of it 33 33 people in chat awesome guys
I'm up here like why do we have to can no one join us like I'm the camera that I don't people aren't coming up
You guys come up
Maybe they don't like
Scared the more I don't hey come hang out with us guys. We won't bite. I won't I won't bite unless you ask me to
I'm just kidding. Oh, because that was my joke. It was a really bad show. I'm so sorry
Let's fight yeah, yeah, I don't know how to fight really I can yell at you
You're like you just you probably just give me that lick of disappointment and you're like your eyes and I just feel terrible
Right. Yeah, it's like that would be that would hurt worse than than yelling at me. You know
Yeah, that's true
I've a lot of empty candles on my table. I just realized it's like a little alter of them
Okay, got it. I'll see you later. I'll see you later. Go this Canada paid us to boycott your panel until he's until he's gets back
Okay, well, I'll see you later then. I'll be back to in the morning three of them. I don't know. We'll have fun
I'll see you in like three hours. Oh
My goodness
Well, good guys go do whatever you want with guys guys. It's not my business. It's none of my business
I'm the only thing I'm worried about is my panel. That's what I'm worried about
Oh, just people are just, just being funny.
I guess I'm going up there in about six minutes
to interrogate Psyche and Paige, that's Sebastian.
Well, I don't know, Sebastian,
are you gonna behave yourself?
Interrogate, yeah.
Give me some truth serum.
Have you ever seen the, you know,
what is sodium pentatol?
And it's like the truth serum.
Yeah, seven and a half.
Yeah, well, there's a movie,
Halloween party or something like that. It's really weird movie. So this guy. It's kind of like it's kind of like a loser guy
Do they have to pay money to join? No
No, the family's open. So you yeah, you sponsored it for the for the for the chat
Yeah, so come up and hang on come play with us
Yes, but this movie so he like this guy so he's like kind of like this guy
He's like kind of like it's overweight kind of dorky guy with like a you know
He is a cat and everything but he's out walking he finds this invitation to a Halloween party. It's like and it's a kind of like artistic and
So he goes and he goes says he like dresses up it goes this Halloween party
then it's like then these like people like they're all these people like like
there's like a woman dressed like probably what's her name like Harley Quinn
and there's there's all these people in costumes and they like they grab the guy
and they like tie him up to the chair they're like all artists and they're
like oh we're gonna like we're gonna do our artistic M-U-R-D-E-R right and
they're and but then you just have to see what happens but so it's really
interesting this this Halloween part it's one of the really good scary movies I
don't know if you ever
I might look it up, but why are you talking so fast? How was it doing that? What's happening?
It was really fast, but I think I was talking fast
No, that wasn't normal. It was like definitely English
It's happening a couple of times though. So maybe now now I don't know
I don't know
Come on. Oh, I'm very white
Yeah, I thought you were gone earlier when you talk to Steve like that.
Oh my god.
Hey, hey, hey, I'm walking here.
No, I'm sorry.
That was really bad.
That was, that was like Tony D'Angelo.
All right.
The Fonz.
That was the Fonz.
Well, I don't know who's cooler, Gaudi or the Fonz?
Jim Carrey?
Gaudi is cool.
But who's cooler?
The Fonz or Gaudi?
Gaudi, probably.
Fonz never hang out with me.
You hear that Fonz, Fonz, Fonzzi?
Um, yeah, I didn't like Fonzzi very much either.
Back to the future.
Uh, just, uh, let's see what's going on.
It's a contest page.
Look, um, what is the contest?
The pin, oh, what is, what is the pin link?
Did I pin something weird?
Hold on.
I'll pin the chat.
I need to change that.
I'm sorry.
I'll fix it.
It's a contest
Well, I like winning so what are we doing just keep paying to be up here like I don't is it?
No, it's not a contest. It's a it's called
Has anybody ever heard of a commercial like okay? Sometimes they have like sponsors like a creative or they have like you know
a producer of things and you know, there's like
It's called it's called like
There we go.
That's just for the people.
I mean, a lot of people like the system.
A lot of people like the system.
If you don't, then you don't have to.
It's my system.
Okay, yep, so perfect.
I think I have the New League hands.
We are open, oh, psyche on point.
Oh, that is funny.
I like that, huh?
There.
There we go. Yeah, I
Sponsored this one Christine. I just didn't know if we had um, I didn't I that's all I knew though
Is that first step? So I didn't know what we did after and what was the point of it other than to make you money
Obviously in like support. Oh, yeah, I'll explain. I'll explain. I'll explain it page. Okay, so I had these open panel. I had these open panels, right?
Yeah, and there were a lot of people coming on. It's like they have very strong personalities
They want to go talk, you know, I should be a better moderator or whatever, right?
But at the same time at the same time, it's like and then it's like oh, that's oh, and you know
I'm letting this person that serves me down
I'm just saying I'd rather talk to people one-on-one and like have my own again
It's because also other people change right other people too. Like I said, they want to press certain people, right? So
I did have one-on-one with start with people and give them the attention also be available for readings one-on-one and not have like
You know have to have people on panel like come on because nobody wants to come up when there's like eight people talking and people have been really
Rude and someone pat my past
Talking it just know when they're fucking screaming stupid shit at each other
And that's but that's what it goes to every day. It happens though. I mean it's like it
So it's like so this is just slowing that process down a little bit where it's like, okay
Well, there's gonna be a sponsor for the panel. They'll get an advertisement for themselves
I'll be more I was basically I was like I really I think I'm about to stop doing the panels all together
I was like I'm about to do so but it's like is there any way I can keep doing them and
Everyone still be happy, and I'm like well if I was kind of if I was
If I was making a little bit a little bit from them, then that would compensate it and then I would not mind
Be having longer panels. I'll say I think it's pretty I think it's pretty pretty generous
You're like three hours five dollars right now. I changed it three hours for five dollars
The other channels do this or pals
Think I think it's a revolutionary. I think I'm maybe the first maybe I'm the first person, but it's like I'm a revolutionary
I'm all I came up with the idea you guys anyone's welcome to try it on their channel, but that's the thing
We live in America. We're allowed to try different things and I'm I've experimented with a lot of different things
It's a me thing. I'll take, I'll take heed for it. You know, he already had a show saying,
oh, pay me money to talk to me. And then he likes, you know, didn't say my name, but he
likes, he was like screaming about it. And then, you know, talk to Joe Shipley about it and stuff.
And so, and like, like, low key likes it. Like, I think some people like the system. And I, you
know, it doesn't bother me any, I just didn't, I just wanted to, and now I know how it works.
Horrible we were talking about Canadian dollar here. Okay, so I love this deck. It's a muse tarot. It was really expensive and super pretty
But anyways in US it's 2699 and
In Canada it's we paid 35 paid 40 fucking dollars for it
Is that what it says? Is it 40 next to it?
Wait to your face that this is how much you're getting ripped off, because you live here.
But isn't the exchange rate a little different, so that's what it accounts for?
I always remember on books, it would always say Canadian price on the book,
but it usually be like $1 off.
Yeah.
Or really like $1 different.
It's just really ignorant.
We should like standardize.
2599 to 3599.
I used to hate that we'd go to the bookstore and I'd be like oh I can afford this and then logically I couldn't and I could afford the American price
Yeah, I mean it's weird. I don't know is it the exchange rate because remember that there's the exchange rate on the PayPal a little bit
Because I don't know if that's the same difference
That's crazy
It's like a it's like a tax. It's like a tariff. It's a kind of tax. Exactly. That's what it is. It's a tax
Yeah, nobody likes ways. No
Except the you know tax collector
Yeah, I like tax returns exactly tax returns
But uh, yeah, I don't know like for when you get monetized on YouTube you have to fill out tax forms and stuff like that
So it's okay. Casey's good. You know, Casey's banned from my my chat
I don't think I've ever read for Casey and he's not interested in it. He's just interested in like promoting himself
I am nice have to have Casey on the show after everyone told me not to have his ass on because of his like domestic violence
background, but anyway, so
That's that that's that bye Casey
Don't let the door hit you where the good lords play. Yeah
That's funny. Oh
You know what I was gonna say something and now I forgot some mental case this big forehead and there's just air in there
Smoke another one bro. I have the munchies. I have sun chips. I should eat them
You should eat them. Oh, I'd really like sun chips. Yeah, those are if they haven't met a subway
Get those
I'm getting hungry. I'm hungry too. I should have went to town now. I can't cuz everything's closed
They don't have been stuff around you
I think I live like 40 kilometers from everything
You can't come delivery
Door-dash, door-dash of dreams. Oh
Sucks
They don't have delivery they have a pizza you can get or something I had delivery or something
They I mean you can't they have something out there. I'm sure it's like you live in the middle of the boonies
It's okay
Pizza pops no
Is it like
Like pizza on a lollipop
These things
Oh, I think I call hot pockets here hot pockets a pot pocket
He says we're in a hungry bunch shows up for lunch. What are you gonna pick hot pockets?
My cast staring at me like from around the corner
Maybe maybe later
No creep? Wow
No, the cats really don't they don't mean to kill sometimes they especially like I don't think they really mean to kill unless they're like hungry
I guess for mice but
They will they do it for fun basically
They think it's like a toy and then it's like it breaks. Okay. Oh lobster look at that lobster sound pretty good
Don't know. It's a celebration today is a celebratory day. It's a nice day
Because you know why it's the 21st
Blackjack, okay, $9 a $40 on this expensive
Oh, we have a god I'm coming to the panel
So peeps yo, what's going on?
You guys ready yep, what we're gonna play we're gonna play strip trivia. Oh
No
No, no, no, why not we shouldn't do that. We can do that. We could totally we can totally do that
We just need two more. Yes. We can do it, but we shouldn't no we could totally do it
When it gets too raunchy just put on a robe or something
Then you lost
Well, then you lost then you lost that's how it works
Sorry the PG version
We're ready for what you said
She wanted to play some strip trivia. Oh, she did. Oh my gosh. Yeah, I
Wanted I want to get gaudy down to his black underwear
That would be pretty fucking funny every time you get a question, right? You get to pick somebody to have them take some clothes off
Okay, well, I would always pick myself because I love getting naked
Welcome to the show
Look at we go we do um like it's glow all the balls
Glow golfing and we put little go sticks in the middle of them down this little hole and then they go
Oh, it's a ball. I thought it was the I thought it was ice
No, it's a golf ball. I thought it was a piece of cocaine
pizza and cocaine a
Piece of cocaine
Pizza cocaine actually sounds good
I wish I've had it. It's like it's a little bit. No makes her teeth a little bit numb, but
Otherwise, it's great. You had pink cocaine yet
And I know I did the pure baby oil pink baby oil. It's it's in there, but I didn't have a pure pink cocaine
I had it mix in the baby oil
Why is it pink really it's pink cocaine just because they put I think I think it's just put it in there for like effect
But actually they don't make it but oh must have made it
Brutal shits it out
That's the only way they can get it
No, I'm just kidding. Yeah, maybe it's like that pink salt right from the Himalayas
Yeah, I don't I don't know but it's a good bet because I know and I know these sometimes you will use a fedgerin to cut some stuff
one second and
Did someone say stroke poker?
Yeah, come on guys. Take down your top.
I don't play poker though. I'm just gonna watch. I'm gonna sit and watch.
We need players, we need p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p- p
He's thinking about it. I know. Yeah. Don't talk to me at all
Please get it anyway
We guys are up
Got it your feets. These are gone now Goddy
My feces
Never done it pages pages psychics, you know, she knew right when I was about to put on her
Put her on camera. You knew exactly when yeah, we're not playing strip poker. That's we can't play it
Spunky Spunky Spunky showed way too much already
I saw I saw I saw the underside of Spunky's boobs the other night
I ain't upset
I was I was I was I was I was having fun. I was like
Yeah, go it was people go ghost. I wasn't upset at all. I was I was like cheering
I was I don't think I've ever seen a set of tits like that in my ever ever my 34 years on a movie and the real life
Anywhere ever on the planet. I have
Don't know how do I carry them around right? I had Justin
Yeah, it's bad. I made Justin like I was complaining about my back
And I was like just feel these things like just put them in your hand and feel the weight
And he's like holy shit. How do you carry those around? Yeah?
You're gonna get a picture
You're going to get a picture of Justin's head in between him.
You can't tell which is which.
They're all just like long, slushy things.
You got three of them right there.
Put a nipple on his head.
Yeah, I have three nipples.
I actually have three nipples.
It's called a witch's mark.
Three nipples. Wow. I had a friend who had a third his third nipple pierced and I think that's pretty funny
They used to uh, well, yeah, they used to like poke needles into it on witches because they thought it was like a marker the devil or something
So glad it wasn't bored then
It was a pretty cool party trick
Well, I pierced my navel with like a safety pin when I was like 14 years old
When I was like 11 and don't tell Grace, okay
Also a safety pin and my eyebrow and then a bunch of my friends their noses and their belly buttons and people's parents were
I know they come in with like, you know fabric swatches
So then you suck heat up the panda disinfect it put an ice cube behind whatever sadger piercing through and then
Those are days I once had my like my eyebrow my my librette my tongue my nipples and my navel appears, but
Yeah
No, Sebastian's not big on breasts, but a woman's feet. It's very important to you
Well, you're just you're just disgusting Sebastian leave women's feet alone
You want me to get rid of? No, no, it's fine. Yeah, alright. Just let me know. I mean
If I get annoyed enough, I'll take care of it myself. Yeah, just pull the plug. Yeah, I will
Reflesh them either way morbid though. Yeah, well, it's Sebastian. So if you knew him you'd say I do kind of a little bit
But not enough to just to say certain things. No, so
Not yet. Anyway, he's harmless, but he was trying to get me to ask you to show your feet for him earlier
Nope, I'm not gonna but they're real cute. Just so you know, I'm but they are
They are a little tiny feet. They're only like five and a half
There's a baby.
You got baby feets.
Wearing his little.
Yep.
Fuck, you haven't shown yours yet, have you?
No, I haven't.
That's more private than my underboob, apparently.
Oh, I'll do a video.
I'm showing my bottom of my toes.
I don't want to ruffle any more feathers.
Ghost might have a heart attack and then I'd feel responsible.
No, no, no.
For me, he won't mind.
I'll FaceTime, you guys.
I'll FaceTime in about 10 minutes.
I don't think I knew what to do. We're all in shock. All of our mouths were just open,
smiling like donuts.
And I gotta keep them guessing I knew those motherfuckers in the chat they're face up like all of ours up there
I can't believe it created such a ruckus though. I didn't think people would be like that offended
But you know what girls if you got I knew it and I've never ever this would this never comes out of my mouth because I'm not this girl
but
Just been going through some shit lately and you know what's made me realize I ain't getting any fucking younger
And I'm certainly not gonna look any better at any other age after this 34. Yeah, we have to appreciate what we have
And you know what all we did was just little shake and I didn't even take them out, but I didn't have any to take out
So that was fun. Yeah
That was a fun day. We were wild and we were wild very simple
It was yeah simple
Good old-fashioned fun for 25 minutes on non-stop
Kid police come running in say no
Yeah, you would think I like wet my boobs out the guns or something next time
That's why I can't go in those places
Yeah, you guys are ridiculous. I actually like
I was I did not say no, no, no, one time I didn't say no, you know, it wasn't you, it wasn't you.
Oh, I did think I saw the nipples slip at once. I didn't even get mad about that.
It wasn't a nipple. It wasn't a nipple.
If that didn't happen, God, it would have a screenshot.
Yeah, nipple gate 2025.
It was like actually it was just a it was just a humongous mole. I'm just kidding.
It was my triple nipple.
Hold on I'm Gotti. I'm trying to do that. I'm trying to put you know the song I wrote about you or the song AI
And I wrote I'm gonna I'm trying to make the video for that one
You want 20 bucks
Yes, please
I'm just kidding
Got it. Got it. This is got it. You know what's funny is like like the page and the
Introduction video I made they cost like let me see that cost like 23
So cause almost like 50 bucks, I think to do both of those without the credits I've spent because it's just like super expensive
I didn't know it was
But this other one I think I
You just like no, but the reason is no this one. I mean, it'll be part of the I'm using these
No, well here's what happened page
It was said it said $19 for like a month membership to this thing
So I was like, okay
I'll make it I'll make a bunch of videos if I signed up for it then I made half the video
Right, and then it stopped and it says about her credits and I have to buy like more credit
I like oh, so so and so some of them are more expensive than the others, but still I will
Monetize the video anyway. I can monetize it
I don't know, I'm just saying, like, it's crazy how, like...
You just I love that people are supporting me. I love that you're making money. You know, I mean, it's good
Think think about how expensive it is to produce a music video
If I was to you know, fly to New York and hire an actor and actress and
You know film that film that it was just a million dollars, but now it's like, you know, it's like, you know, 50 bucks is not too bad
It's great. I think yeah, it's fantastic. I do too. It's pretty cool
See so
So let me have a look
What are they saying? Oh, I showed I didn't show you my feet ever
No, you never showed your feet. No, not like intentionally maybe if I was like walking in my little driveway walk with your feet
oopsie
That's not what he's talking about though.
Why are these guys freaking about feet?
What's going on?
They're just chatting.
I'll figure that out by the service.
You know what I mean?
Psyche!
Isaiah!
Psyche, hi!
Psyche, hi! Isaiah, hi!
Hey, we did the same thing, Jesus.
No, no, no, no, I'm not in the woods this time. I'm I'm actually I'm in a bar this time
Yeah, there's there is the lovely bartender and the lovely bartender's boyfriend
Okay, and then the lovely patrons of the bar over here
Ignoring actually there's nobody on the pool table. So this is everybody in the bar right now. Hey guys, cool
Monday night bar scene
It's Monday night, man. I mean like yeah
Actually, it actually was wall-to-wall slam on people we had it was a cornhole
Play that here with a cornhole board board we call it beanbag we call it beanbag
All right, keep your bean flicking to the side, okay?
All right, this was American Cornhole Mondays,
and well, there's a lot of people throwing.
That's only butthole flicking, okay?
Yeah, cornholes, bean flicking, it's all bad.
I know, I know, you know, you know.
Well, it's not that bad, because I mean, it's just cornhole.
But, you know.
Hey.
Hey, look look look
It's all in it's the wait and never mind
Hi, I don't even want to know what he was trying to explain to you guys because he's been saying the most outlandish shit tonight
Him never always
Are you his wife?
I think that's the bartender
I am the bartender. Yes, and yeah, your clothes are actually on for once
So that's that's a plus you might get a gold star by the end of the night
When I was drawing I'm gonna have to pull the video footage from the bar, but he
Was naked in the bar. Oh shit
No, you can't tell psyche
He's gonna fucking, he's gonna send a fucking hit squad up here to fucking take those video tombs.
20 bucks.
He's like the dancing baby.
20 dollars is 20 dollars.
Yaaah. Lee.
I thought it was worth a little more than that. Holy shit.
Well, I don't have like the fucking fifth element fucking like three titties
So I got two normal titties
Two fourth nipples
Bullshit, well, I mean, I guess if it's that long, you know, there's a couple extra dots, but
He's mad at Jennifer. Who's Jennifer motherfuckers you guys asked. Hey, I'm just I
Don't know. I just picked a random name. I'm just getting validated. Is that you
What happened
Well, I just picked a random name. I was like Jennifer sucks nuts. I think he's in the chair. Are you in the chest?
What happened? I don't know what's going on. Can you not hear us?
I can hear you guys
Okay, we're good then
I'm totally sure because I finally got good service. I just got freaked out for a second. What's going on?
I don't know what's up. What's that butter? What up butter cup less? What up God the bitch?
You don't like me, you know that love
Yes, they didn't see what happens
You know, I'm like, oh what they say son of a bitch. Oh motherfucking guy, whatever we need when they bash God. Oh
Don't pick on Gotti. Who muted me
It's like he's doing weird stuff. I don't know what's up
Yeah, she was well mobile panel. You don't want to say nothing. You don't want to speak
I said I saw the video
It was kind of weak, I don't know why you posted it
Exposed I see what she's doing. I know what you're doing. I don't know why you're doing it to him
I he doesn't do anything to you
But whatever you guys say people get paid out some people get bought out
It looked like he was bought out by a lot. So, you know, I'm gonna keep it up there
This is what I'm talking about. You keep pushing shit man. Why do you keep pushing shit?
Why I keep talking shit
Did for 14 minutes 14 minutes. Well, where were we pushing it though? We weren't pushing it anywhere. Oh
probably did
We'll sit there whatever you're the one trying to push it up. You don't have a gender you're the one creating it man
Enjoy it. Enjoy what happened?
It's whatever dude, don't bring it here. We'll handle it somewhere else
You bump it up, I'll just shut it
Well, this is not that will do what you want. I'm gonna get a chocolate bar
All right, faggot page got bless you smoke you got bless you
Go suck three dicks
Just go just go faggot
Sponk you guys ready? Yeah
What are we ready for?
What do you mean? I was gonna call you guys. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, we're ready. Oh forget it now
I mean shit. You don't want me. I thought you were talking about strip poker again. Honestly
Is his phone charged
Let me look hang on. Yeah, I have a second device. Oh you got two devices
Sebastian just come up and do your bullshit routine. Come on up
Before we go let's Sebastian up for two minutes. Yeah, just so you can get this shit off his fucking chest
This guy's obsessed. He's one of those rain men type of guys. He's gonna keep talking about it all night
Let's go. What are you doing? Hey, it's gonna ask you about your feet and just humor for two minutes if you don't
You special needs
Fucking meat look bad
No, no, no, no, you just get it just humor for two minutes. Trust me
Cry
Well, go ahead then come on up Sebastian. This is your time to shine
What's that?
Who ripped one?
If I ripped one I'd be laughing
Okay, you there will be signs does that say glow in the dark you guys see it
We have glow this we would do glow night and like so go play in the dark and fucking put glow sticks in this little hole
And then you can see the balls all night. Oh you put the glow sticks in there. Oh, I thought the ball
Okay, okay, that's cool. I went to read the chat for a second. And where are we putting those sticks?
Sebastian you got two minutes to hurry up. Let's go. What's this is this is this is this the video
The docking the docking dongs
What what cards are you guys gonna be paid page did you pick a card in his deck?
No, or maybe you'll just assign them
His tarot deck, he's making he's making that tarot deck. Oh
Did you pick them? I'm sure he'd probably let me I didn't think about it. I didn't ask
Like are you there?
What doing? I have a question.
What doing?
Do I just put my hand up?
Excuse me sir.
Excuse me.
Professor Psyche, may I go to the bathroom?
Great, you'd be great teachers like they'll be pissed on the floor. They'll be chaos and mayhem. Oh, yeah
I'm not gonna lie. I think that all of us would probably if you have our little hand in that anarchy in that room
Run supervised. We'd slip out the window. Well, yeah, I'd probably get out there before I got caught for sure
But I
Behaved I just talked too much. They called me mouth in the south
Did you snitch? No, never. Just chatty. I'd have to block you if you did.
No, not a snitch. I'd have to block you if you did such thing. Snitches get stitches.
Yeah, we all get stitches. Take it to the grave. What is this town happening here?
I don't know. Somebody's backstage. Maybe Sebastian.
Yeah, I'm making a deal
He's like you can see Paige's feet and you can rest about it, but you've got to send me $20 cash app
Oh shit. He's pipping off feet now
Charming psych I'll come to your house and I'll fucking up bus kneecaps for that money. I'm kidding
Big profit hustle of my little toes. Yeah, right
Oh Tom flashes here. Wow
Tom come on up
I'm leaving
Penal about to get lit
Like when I had Paige what run page runs. Yeah, it's gonna get rough up here
Let's go
Why do I feel like we're about to be under attack it feels like I feel like my heart just be started being really fast
Yeah, something things about to go down something's up. I
Am
You feel it oh see here we go
I don't know what's going on.
Carrier?
Easy, take that picture off.
You like to bitch about pictures, take that picture off.
Stephanie!
Yes, hi Sebastian
No, yo, you punk. What's up, man?
page
Good to see you page
It comes to purve two minutes now go ahead Sebastian unfortunately, I can't say the same for gaudi
I'm not too happy to see him but pretend. I'm not even here Tom flash
Pretend. I'm not even here guys. Go ahead
Make it all on a second here. Is that the real Tom flash or is it like a let me make a few adjustments here
I don't know. It looks like something moving on down
Don't say I didn't warn you man. I mean fuck you ain't nobody, right?
Daddy's God
I
Did is a delinquent
It's a criminal
Don't worry about the thief worry about you
As a matter of fact spunky my private detectives have uncovered some dirt on Gotti recently
Are ya oh, yeah, we've got him on many things
What's Tom doing?
Tom he's talking about Joel Wigan. Oh this one
All that time
Is it him
Flash at the real-time flesh. Yeah, he's not one to be quiet like this Eddie. Is that you Eddie?
Maybe a good guy he's actually a good guy that Eddie
Yeah, I don't say that too often though. Unlike you, Gotti. What's your problem Sebastian?
What is your problem? You're talking crap about me in the side chat there
I was down in the side chat you tried to make yourself look good at my expense, didn't you?
What happened in your life that you have to come down on?